[
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7552493526 and 9006992656?",
    "answer": 16559486182
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 33127 and 72165?",
    "answer": 105292
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7 and 4?",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8901358 and 8019217?",
    "answer": 16920575
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8129147482 and 8217679555?",
    "answer": 16346827037
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 29028458 and 20383168?",
    "answer": 49411626
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 872895107 and 633945082?",
    "answer": 1506840189
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 16 and 37?",
    "answer": 53
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7113636 and 3977958?",
    "answer": 11091594
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7077 and 8975?",
    "answer": 16052
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 53498208 and 58836208?",
    "answer": 112334416
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 14 and 73?",
    "answer": 87
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4028108632 and 7751201500?",
    "answer": 11779310132
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8206 and 8086?",
    "answer": 16292
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 61355924 and 24166168?",
    "answer": 85522092
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 78 and 98?",
    "answer": 176
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 11 and 23?",
    "answer": 34
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 64389879 and 52736913?",
    "answer": 117126792
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4451051 and 5057789?",
    "answer": 9508840
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6 and 1?",
    "answer": 7
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4406249 and 4021822?",
    "answer": 8428071
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 268637 and 477858?",
    "answer": 746495
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3320734 and 5578761?",
    "answer": 8899495
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 70924156 and 25335504?",
    "answer": 96259660
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 31 and 63?",
    "answer": 94
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 41980652 and 59962446?",
    "answer": 101943098
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2402786 and 4888122?",
    "answer": 7290908
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 50464851 and 35450224?",
    "answer": 85915075
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 429 and 860?",
    "answer": 1289
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 59514630 and 96166572?",
    "answer": 155681202
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4671541547 and 9388114769?",
    "answer": 14059656316
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 228581256 and 706664105?",
    "answer": 935245361
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 138 and 507?",
    "answer": 645
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 41302 and 18754?",
    "answer": 60056
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1 and 6?",
    "answer": 7
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8544046 and 5739911?",
    "answer": 14283957
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5811 and 2680?",
    "answer": 8491
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 592516 and 239428?",
    "answer": 831944
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8554 and 7701?",
    "answer": 16255
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9869542 and 3864227?",
    "answer": 13733769
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8463017 and 3523389?",
    "answer": 11986406
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8 and 5?",
    "answer": 13
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 24072989 and 88699670?",
    "answer": 112772659
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 685886008 and 971234180?",
    "answer": 1657120188
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 76427 and 20780?",
    "answer": 97207
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 647 and 161?",
    "answer": 808
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 23473305 and 34085206?",
    "answer": 57558511
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5 and 7?",
    "answer": 12
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 30092 and 32362?",
    "answer": 62454
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 527 and 742?",
    "answer": 1269
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 72503 and 72069?",
    "answer": 144572
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3 and 8?",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 90 and 52?",
    "answer": 142
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 76 and 21?",
    "answer": 97
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 174 and 422?",
    "answer": 596
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2 and 4?",
    "answer": 6
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 46588561 and 74091677?",
    "answer": 120680238
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 171049 and 791675?",
    "answer": 962724
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 89 and 77?",
    "answer": 166
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 778462054 and 178874074?",
    "answer": 957336128
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 66 and 62?",
    "answer": 128
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3 and 5?",
    "answer": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6 and 4?",
    "answer": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 638300323 and 891089989?",
    "answer": 1529390312
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7 and 9?",
    "answer": 16
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2621713652 and 6351385269?",
    "answer": 8973098921
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5484 and 3586?",
    "answer": 9070
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8 and 4?",
    "answer": 12
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 870989 and 452150?",
    "answer": 1323139
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 720 and 890?",
    "answer": 1610
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5128046688 and 1479402903?",
    "answer": 6607449591
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 48068604 and 54416647?",
    "answer": 102485251
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1 and 4?",
    "answer": 5
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3287 and 9963?",
    "answer": 13250
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 19534585 and 39483591?",
    "answer": 59018176
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 799 and 586?",
    "answer": 1385
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 594172419 and 926038353?",
    "answer": 1520210772
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 151756785 and 782064241?",
    "answer": 933821026
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2772352432 and 4398058645?",
    "answer": 7170411077
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 181062952 and 448021568?",
    "answer": 629084520
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9 and 5?",
    "answer": 14
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8845792 and 1317350?",
    "answer": 10163142
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 30203988 and 23435111?",
    "answer": 53639099
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5 and 1?",
    "answer": 6
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 94691 and 94405?",
    "answer": 189096
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 204840543 and 198053324?",
    "answer": 402893867
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 784352 and 224947?",
    "answer": 1009299
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1715853361 and 5791544339?",
    "answer": 7507397700
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 80928603 and 58974323?",
    "answer": 139902926
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4248 and 8708?",
    "answer": 12956
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6 and 5?",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 821 and 388?",
    "answer": 1209
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 79242 and 74050?",
    "answer": 153292
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9 and 3?",
    "answer": 12
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 68356431 and 65579502?",
    "answer": 133935933
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 898 and 319?",
    "answer": 1217
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 30515 and 62381?",
    "answer": 92896
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 89871 and 19288?",
    "answer": 109159
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 828950 and 580895?",
    "answer": 1409845
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 49106372 and 98379269?",
    "answer": 147485641
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 731541 and 420146?",
    "answer": 1151687
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 440373359 and 767493433?",
    "answer": 1207866792
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 339505395 and 567309753?",
    "answer": 906815148
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1 and 9?",
    "answer": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5740503 and 7940387?",
    "answer": 13680890
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 460 and 590?",
    "answer": 1050
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 291 and 515?",
    "answer": 806
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2257285 and 4928628?",
    "answer": 7185913
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 250 and 511?",
    "answer": 761
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6213053 and 9462410?",
    "answer": 15675463
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4063675 and 1685838?",
    "answer": 5749513
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2529717 and 5205070?",
    "answer": 7734787
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 194325 and 826056?",
    "answer": 1020381
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 39371 and 14465?",
    "answer": 53836
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1286734 and 9211695?",
    "answer": 10498429
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5806 and 3328?",
    "answer": 9134
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 550467485 and 672817209?",
    "answer": 1223284694
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1496313770 and 5300361149?",
    "answer": 6796674919
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 95 and 16?",
    "answer": 111
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 30459 and 39986?",
    "answer": 70445
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7915825213 and 7856553989?",
    "answer": 15772379202
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 499152 and 875357?",
    "answer": 1374509
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 53900 and 23053?",
    "answer": 76953
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 160854 and 284530?",
    "answer": 445384
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 390738 and 367488?",
    "answer": 758226
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4808636031 and 1995823255?",
    "answer": 6804459286
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3906 and 9945?",
    "answer": 13851
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 348 and 508?",
    "answer": 856
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 40760 and 85036?",
    "answer": 125796
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 90461773 and 46592606?",
    "answer": 137054379
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6 and 7?",
    "answer": 13
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5024875 and 9044041?",
    "answer": 14068916
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7157 and 2695?",
    "answer": 9852
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 482 and 723?",
    "answer": 1205
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2910922403 and 1200132036?",
    "answer": 4111054439
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4818 and 6001?",
    "answer": 10819
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 45136031 and 44245829?",
    "answer": 89381860
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6558198222 and 3923884003?",
    "answer": 10482082225
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8356382 and 9284525?",
    "answer": 17640907
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 21215294 and 81678773?",
    "answer": 102894067
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8829657 and 7369969?",
    "answer": 16199626
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 366 and 952?",
    "answer": 1318
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 56710 and 16757?",
    "answer": 73467
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 85 and 77?",
    "answer": 162
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 69 and 78?",
    "answer": 147
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 773084657 and 695243456?",
    "answer": 1468328113
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3298614875 and 3373851148?",
    "answer": 6672466023
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3268411053 and 4890180811?",
    "answer": 8158591864
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 48845665 and 72927236?",
    "answer": 121772901
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3350 and 9810?",
    "answer": 13160
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 92522601 and 54782308?",
    "answer": 147304909
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 86 and 37?",
    "answer": 123
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4025 and 1919?",
    "answer": 5944
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 65493 and 30511?",
    "answer": 96004
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 835 and 689?",
    "answer": 1524
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 45 and 55?",
    "answer": 100
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4706936762 and 3585405046?",
    "answer": 8292341808
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 186211 and 735782?",
    "answer": 921993
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 20041701 and 54138695?",
    "answer": 74180396
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2961715 and 6348457?",
    "answer": 9310172
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 38179 and 85361?",
    "answer": 123540
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1777 and 6089?",
    "answer": 7866
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5777678 and 6782476?",
    "answer": 12560154
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 573821396 and 340592533?",
    "answer": 914413929
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 375 and 952?",
    "answer": 1327
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 356672505 and 474268888?",
    "answer": 830941393
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6886766221 and 8101973917?",
    "answer": 14988740138
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1 and 7?",
    "answer": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3127676 and 5414676?",
    "answer": 8542352
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 721805 and 521777?",
    "answer": 1243582
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 91 and 87?",
    "answer": 178
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 43988243 and 97070358?",
    "answer": 141058601
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3270646 and 8212920?",
    "answer": 11483566
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 925167236 and 819448374?",
    "answer": 1744615610
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 561669 and 421652?",
    "answer": 983321
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7975000 and 8774355?",
    "answer": 16749355
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 18 and 51?",
    "answer": 69
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 72 and 96?",
    "answer": 168
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9619950 and 1310707?",
    "answer": 10930657
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 471750 and 710127?",
    "answer": 1181877
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 224235 and 898957?",
    "answer": 1123192
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 351150 and 825478?",
    "answer": 1176628
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2 and 8?",
    "answer": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 364 and 229?",
    "answer": 593
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6 and 7?",
    "answer": 13
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 55524 and 55728?",
    "answer": 111252
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 43 and 17?",
    "answer": 60
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 892119 and 246600?",
    "answer": 1138719
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9885403 and 3493362?",
    "answer": 13378765
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 33 and 25?",
    "answer": 58
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 278216977 and 526063621?",
    "answer": 804280598
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 315 and 700?",
    "answer": 1015
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 99 and 46?",
    "answer": 145
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 405 and 690?",
    "answer": 1095
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 35 and 19?",
    "answer": 54
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 80835 and 93560?",
    "answer": 174395
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6387441 and 1579565?",
    "answer": 7967006
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4802 and 8584?",
    "answer": 13386
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 356819 and 740893?",
    "answer": 1097712
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4150451657 and 4349292613?",
    "answer": 8499744270
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 344712 and 301394?",
    "answer": 646106
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 94335526 and 80519913?",
    "answer": 174855439
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 579311 and 208189?",
    "answer": 787500
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3485 and 8736?",
    "answer": 12221
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 575 and 502?",
    "answer": 1077
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 43465 and 49628?",
    "answer": 93093
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 811 and 169?",
    "answer": 980
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 37680785 and 94660204?",
    "answer": 132340989
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 235003748 and 956348021?",
    "answer": 1191351769
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 57863458 and 32276205?",
    "answer": 90139663
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 726201546 and 485075002?",
    "answer": 1211276548
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4 and 4?",
    "answer": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2 and 7?",
    "answer": 9
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 23216302 and 67009609?",
    "answer": 90225911
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9744162 and 7314292?",
    "answer": 17058454
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 782839 and 651996?",
    "answer": 1434835
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 214551704 and 471758096?",
    "answer": 686309800
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1095032 and 9169670?",
    "answer": 10264702
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 168 and 266?",
    "answer": 434
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 410610774 and 976987992?",
    "answer": 1387598766
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 529182882 and 318627804?",
    "answer": 847810686
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5 and 1?",
    "answer": 6
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6731 and 3624?",
    "answer": 10355
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 62852963 and 47954755?",
    "answer": 110807718
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4 and 2?",
    "answer": 6
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 71925 and 20433?",
    "answer": 92358
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 965344322 and 301909630?",
    "answer": 1267253952
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4931 and 9474?",
    "answer": 14405
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9 and 8?",
    "answer": 17
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2481719083 and 8721829226?",
    "answer": 11203548309
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 46953 and 23910?",
    "answer": 70863
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 714 and 680?",
    "answer": 1394
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1235302 and 2986243?",
    "answer": 4221545
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 345 and 746?",
    "answer": 1091
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9104173 and 5119639?",
    "answer": 14223812
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 437735 and 790352?",
    "answer": 1228087
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1773 and 7337?",
    "answer": 9110
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 836116788 and 597472051?",
    "answer": 1433588839
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1935228 and 6723191?",
    "answer": 8658419
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8654 and 1781?",
    "answer": 10435
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5841383656 and 8588894902?",
    "answer": 14430278558
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 89 and 77?",
    "answer": 166
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 379676 and 292859?",
    "answer": 672535
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5934074 and 6324433?",
    "answer": 12258507
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2087314 and 7136090?",
    "answer": 9223404
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 231920960 and 699037510?",
    "answer": 930958470
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1 and 9?",
    "answer": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 993160313 and 467034252?",
    "answer": 1460194565
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1913 and 3475?",
    "answer": 5388
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2993210191 and 1590596326?",
    "answer": 4583806517
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9856012809 and 1486038463?",
    "answer": 11342051272
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 14 and 80?",
    "answer": 94
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 863 and 797?",
    "answer": 1660
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 51 and 67?",
    "answer": 118
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 662 and 995?",
    "answer": 1657
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 97165 and 75751?",
    "answer": 172916
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 33209 and 23745?",
    "answer": 56954
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 884127 and 698220?",
    "answer": 1582347
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 28971 and 95791?",
    "answer": 124762
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 423114780 and 966019439?",
    "answer": 1389134219
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 975095948 and 728600125?",
    "answer": 1703696073
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 39269 and 29713?",
    "answer": 68982
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 931899622 and 749741199?",
    "answer": 1681640821
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 115204329 and 769802651?",
    "answer": 885006980
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8 and 8?",
    "answer": 16
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4431 and 4866?",
    "answer": 9297
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 295 and 825?",
    "answer": 1120
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2350692 and 9100418?",
    "answer": 11451110
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2364360649 and 8955647048?",
    "answer": 11320007697
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 926268 and 425453?",
    "answer": 1351721
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 95 and 41?",
    "answer": 136
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3312784 and 1394253?",
    "answer": 4707037
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8 and 1?",
    "answer": 9
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 597 and 913?",
    "answer": 1510
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 584 and 675?",
    "answer": 1259
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6292136 and 5131016?",
    "answer": 11423152
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 42 and 63?",
    "answer": 105
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 355714 and 662181?",
    "answer": 1017895
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 26 and 83?",
    "answer": 109
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 45679 and 52829?",
    "answer": 98508
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 74080646 and 74214490?",
    "answer": 148295136
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4346969783 and 8397253446?",
    "answer": 12744223229
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 990868930 and 336799346?",
    "answer": 1327668276
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 47 and 21?",
    "answer": 68
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4 and 9?",
    "answer": 13
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8 and 6?",
    "answer": 14
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 24834553 and 68966530?",
    "answer": 93801083
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 18 and 96?",
    "answer": 114
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 237458 and 377094?",
    "answer": 614552
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 235 and 529?",
    "answer": 764
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8589402921 and 8699219800?",
    "answer": 17288622721
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6 and 3?",
    "answer": 9
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7085250270 and 5561068017?",
    "answer": 12646318287
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 78705 and 77657?",
    "answer": 156362
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7019312 and 2956392?",
    "answer": 9975704
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 12588 and 97701?",
    "answer": 110289
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 61 and 65?",
    "answer": 126
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 14549 and 81044?",
    "answer": 95593
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 96568 and 39467?",
    "answer": 136035
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6172760062 and 5477842436?",
    "answer": 11650602498
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5 and 9?",
    "answer": 14
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 290450341 and 719984545?",
    "answer": 1010434886
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 137253 and 294910?",
    "answer": 432163
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5093595431 and 3996132199?",
    "answer": 9089727630
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8 and 6?",
    "answer": 14
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 850597 and 626630?",
    "answer": 1477227
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 126705 and 614584?",
    "answer": 741289
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 71300 and 49408?",
    "answer": 120708
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 724 and 305?",
    "answer": 1029
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 30601 and 90245?",
    "answer": 120846
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 549850 and 162168?",
    "answer": 712018
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6405788765 and 1447908229?",
    "answer": 7853696994
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7348 and 1047?",
    "answer": 8395
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 797906888 and 118274183?",
    "answer": 916181071
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3268128577 and 2390927078?",
    "answer": 5659055655
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5475437 and 6253439?",
    "answer": 11728876
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4428259 and 6258523?",
    "answer": 10686782
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 84019590 and 77666910?",
    "answer": 161686500
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 584771 and 999119?",
    "answer": 1583890
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 503836 and 790223?",
    "answer": 1294059
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4411077 and 1535083?",
    "answer": 5946160
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 418623966 and 615112019?",
    "answer": 1033735985
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1072 and 2856?",
    "answer": 3928
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6795941 and 8269430?",
    "answer": 15065371
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4195 and 5054?",
    "answer": 9249
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 838 and 884?",
    "answer": 1722
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 918241 and 819589?",
    "answer": 1737830
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3175380996 and 1265463554?",
    "answer": 4440844550
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4823 and 3374?",
    "answer": 8197
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 206419894 and 271059655?",
    "answer": 477479549
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 53845 and 19921?",
    "answer": 73766
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 38 and 45?",
    "answer": 83
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1262961803 and 9820994966?",
    "answer": 11083956769
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7395979 and 4314673?",
    "answer": 11710652
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 712982902 and 235778061?",
    "answer": 948760963
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7334122283 and 8365650454?",
    "answer": 15699772737
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 637480463 and 445879812?",
    "answer": 1083360275
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8946461972 and 1558181788?",
    "answer": 10504643760
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 56763438 and 34971097?",
    "answer": 91734535
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 356584561 and 408386532?",
    "answer": 764971093
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 871577 and 374541?",
    "answer": 1246118
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 67 and 53?",
    "answer": 120
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 24720111 and 36174625?",
    "answer": 60894736
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3183359175 and 8400302608?",
    "answer": 11583661783
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 35900890 and 62468115?",
    "answer": 98369005
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 20520 and 73000?",
    "answer": 93520
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 53581694 and 95142177?",
    "answer": 148723871
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 733312 and 896451?",
    "answer": 1629763
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7188 and 3673?",
    "answer": 10861
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1849581872 and 4216531853?",
    "answer": 6066113725
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 418676531 and 446642869?",
    "answer": 865319400
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1251437 and 5795839?",
    "answer": 7047276
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 23 and 65?",
    "answer": 88
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 67220809 and 72159924?",
    "answer": 139380733
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 641 and 804?",
    "answer": 1445
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9 and 3?",
    "answer": 12
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 15211 and 99656?",
    "answer": 114867
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 12825 and 22284?",
    "answer": 35109
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 727 and 810?",
    "answer": 1537
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6937678 and 1269105?",
    "answer": 8206783
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 76874959 and 63266117?",
    "answer": 140141076
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6834599 and 8246216?",
    "answer": 15080815
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 98149 and 81211?",
    "answer": 179360
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 16 and 92?",
    "answer": 108
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 262729206 and 816215733?",
    "answer": 1078944939
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4283465 and 4001962?",
    "answer": 8285427
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9704089789 and 2079335753?",
    "answer": 11783425542
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 535708 and 897197?",
    "answer": 1432905
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4868 and 1290?",
    "answer": 6158
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4456 and 5581?",
    "answer": 10037
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 88 and 25?",
    "answer": 113
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8 and 1?",
    "answer": 9
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3007 and 9010?",
    "answer": 12017
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7665 and 4906?",
    "answer": 12571
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8945021 and 5799234?",
    "answer": 14744255
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8041694 and 4479148?",
    "answer": 12520842
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6869732 and 1546959?",
    "answer": 8416691
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8 and 3?",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3757390 and 3197316?",
    "answer": 6954706
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4 and 6?",
    "answer": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 77986757 and 96129566?",
    "answer": 174116323
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 72 and 85?",
    "answer": 157
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 436634 and 838202?",
    "answer": 1274836
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 476891 and 851347?",
    "answer": 1328238
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8105 and 6342?",
    "answer": 14447
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5662 and 5603?",
    "answer": 11265
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2763105 and 6769630?",
    "answer": 9532735
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1691407809 and 3863565357?",
    "answer": 5554973166
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 52 and 59?",
    "answer": 111
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2284286459 and 8681649752?",
    "answer": 10965936211
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 65 and 51?",
    "answer": 116
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 608542097 and 565090043?",
    "answer": 1173632140
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 79743 and 47160?",
    "answer": 126903
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 27195 and 42220?",
    "answer": 69415
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4819590 and 3968704?",
    "answer": 8788294
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7186900814 and 6552589271?",
    "answer": 13739490085
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3430206 and 5608381?",
    "answer": 9038587
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 81857803 and 83166424?",
    "answer": 165024227
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8 and 3?",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4892 and 7793?",
    "answer": 12685
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 889 and 214?",
    "answer": 1103
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2752 and 2817?",
    "answer": 5569
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4695 and 1299?",
    "answer": 5994
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1773923185 and 7250001092?",
    "answer": 9023924277
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 785 and 889?",
    "answer": 1674
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5 and 8?",
    "answer": 13
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 44705 and 53383?",
    "answer": 98088
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6 and 1?",
    "answer": 7
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 77 and 69?",
    "answer": 146
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 42 and 28?",
    "answer": 70
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 893680 and 650080?",
    "answer": 1543760
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8887888 and 5733292?",
    "answer": 14621180
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 65182 and 63497?",
    "answer": 128679
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6511 and 3589?",
    "answer": 10100
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 889779234 and 296364693?",
    "answer": 1186143927
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3542404665 and 4989822532?",
    "answer": 8532227197
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 50187 and 18516?",
    "answer": 68703
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 14857 and 32661?",
    "answer": 47518
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9831519 and 2727955?",
    "answer": 12559474
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5187004238 and 5981610546?",
    "answer": 11168614784
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9541849771 and 7850932841?",
    "answer": 17392782612
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4451 and 7310?",
    "answer": 11761
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 17 and 88?",
    "answer": 105
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 380 and 707?",
    "answer": 1087
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6040 and 9281?",
    "answer": 15321
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 701967 and 149367?",
    "answer": 851334
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 994110954 and 282091351?",
    "answer": 1276202305
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 809 and 681?",
    "answer": 1490
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4432323 and 4182054?",
    "answer": 8614377
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5 and 3?",
    "answer": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2 and 7?",
    "answer": 9
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 13503 and 87029?",
    "answer": 100532
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 50453 and 34865?",
    "answer": 85318
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 178654 and 427593?",
    "answer": 606247
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 67407660 and 12096355?",
    "answer": 79504015
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 46538342 and 60258637?",
    "answer": 106796979
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 81 and 47?",
    "answer": 128
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 330 and 186?",
    "answer": 516
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 74348857 and 25776685?",
    "answer": 100125542
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 48 and 82?",
    "answer": 130
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 462472 and 924374?",
    "answer": 1386846
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 52944596 and 69769016?",
    "answer": 122713612
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1571909555 and 1681444150?",
    "answer": 3253353705
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 58492135 and 47238158?",
    "answer": 105730293
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1862 and 1305?",
    "answer": 3167
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 498 and 959?",
    "answer": 1457
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 794 and 210?",
    "answer": 1004
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 660071967 and 812629824?",
    "answer": 1472701791
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 27479040 and 15409076?",
    "answer": 42888116
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9029440 and 3862664?",
    "answer": 12892104
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 420191 and 782315?",
    "answer": 1202506
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 54176629 and 94508932?",
    "answer": 148685561
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4531707 and 1618883?",
    "answer": 6150590
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 71872 and 17126?",
    "answer": 88998
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 445 and 520?",
    "answer": 965
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9112580 and 4450522?",
    "answer": 13563102
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 775016 and 594931?",
    "answer": 1369947
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4 and 5?",
    "answer": 9
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6532529 and 7392834?",
    "answer": 13925363
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 49240447 and 48734342?",
    "answer": 97974789
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 628252095 and 141997211?",
    "answer": 770249306
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4 and 8?",
    "answer": 12
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5522895374 and 4081283712?",
    "answer": 9604179086
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 171226 and 318921?",
    "answer": 490147
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 488100 and 201302?",
    "answer": 689402
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9866422 and 8058325?",
    "answer": 17924747
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2 and 6?",
    "answer": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3218516986 and 7175518809?",
    "answer": 10394035795
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 504661224 and 275911768?",
    "answer": 780572992
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 462573 and 428766?",
    "answer": 891339
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 18777 and 86728?",
    "answer": 105505
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4822 and 6708?",
    "answer": 11530
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2 and 1?",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4 and 8?",
    "answer": 12
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1 and 9?",
    "answer": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 315389059 and 976455419?",
    "answer": 1291844478
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2725 and 3753?",
    "answer": 6478
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 782195 and 960488?",
    "answer": 1742683
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9 and 1?",
    "answer": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3 and 7?",
    "answer": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 71886568 and 11296787?",
    "answer": 83183355
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4149247098 and 3792525215?",
    "answer": 7941772313
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2281 and 5974?",
    "answer": 8255
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 858 and 567?",
    "answer": 1425
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9716418395 and 5587519496?",
    "answer": 15303937891
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8 and 1?",
    "answer": 9
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 683514721 and 789252169?",
    "answer": 1472766890
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 66 and 32?",
    "answer": 98
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 767 and 550?",
    "answer": 1317
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 26893 and 99509?",
    "answer": 126402
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7 and 8?",
    "answer": 15
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 50 and 89?",
    "answer": 139
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 397551 and 204930?",
    "answer": 602481
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 55108 and 20161?",
    "answer": 75269
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 94 and 82?",
    "answer": 176
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 60 and 68?",
    "answer": 128
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9311584 and 3006654?",
    "answer": 12318238
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 55920731 and 30161618?",
    "answer": 86082349
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 347329 and 864756?",
    "answer": 1212085
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 97313 and 50934?",
    "answer": 148247
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 804403 and 160873?",
    "answer": 965276
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 752 and 372?",
    "answer": 1124
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 700347873 and 619276338?",
    "answer": 1319624211
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 737584342 and 969085029?",
    "answer": 1706669371
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4086 and 6453?",
    "answer": 10539
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 131 and 655?",
    "answer": 786
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 607 and 221?",
    "answer": 828
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9397 and 3987?",
    "answer": 13384
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 977041 and 128711?",
    "answer": 1105752
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 746487 and 683650?",
    "answer": 1430137
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1117253 and 6280122?",
    "answer": 7397375
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8183367 and 7543985?",
    "answer": 15727352
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 973078 and 405043?",
    "answer": 1378121
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1 and 4?",
    "answer": 5
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 635067 and 937977?",
    "answer": 1573044
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 65 and 94?",
    "answer": 159
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 61 and 33?",
    "answer": 94
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 71 and 71?",
    "answer": 142
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 496 and 444?",
    "answer": 940
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2 and 6?",
    "answer": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 46567 and 96085?",
    "answer": 142652
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 48 and 47?",
    "answer": 95
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 50 and 88?",
    "answer": 138
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1325591393 and 9004096042?",
    "answer": 10329687435
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 330 and 700?",
    "answer": 1030
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 65417 and 42759?",
    "answer": 108176
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4871 and 4194?",
    "answer": 9065
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 44531 and 26799?",
    "answer": 71330
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 853074 and 106958?",
    "answer": 960032
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 917 and 809?",
    "answer": 1726
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 74482 and 48040?",
    "answer": 122522
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 980281148 and 792636027?",
    "answer": 1772917175
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 835 and 731?",
    "answer": 1566
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 591113492 and 792688358?",
    "answer": 1383801850
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2646 and 1832?",
    "answer": 4478
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4991418601 and 7781872898?",
    "answer": 12773291499
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 983144632 and 596901376?",
    "answer": 1580046008
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 711706174 and 923088903?",
    "answer": 1634795077
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 86204 and 39730?",
    "answer": 125934
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2867 and 4037?",
    "answer": 6904
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2601417084 and 2332331262?",
    "answer": 4933748346
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 925 and 752?",
    "answer": 1677
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 41 and 68?",
    "answer": 109
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 77685 and 19389?",
    "answer": 97074
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2441488343 and 6905626246?",
    "answer": 9347114589
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6471 and 3246?",
    "answer": 9717
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 91782022 and 68890166?",
    "answer": 160672188
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 29 and 30?",
    "answer": 59
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 25355806 and 95154787?",
    "answer": 120510593
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3523928975 and 6250354762?",
    "answer": 9774283737
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6126558 and 3674379?",
    "answer": 9800937
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3 and 2?",
    "answer": 5
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7574915295 and 1528128740?",
    "answer": 9103044035
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1575596 and 8642804?",
    "answer": 10218400
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9998 and 4155?",
    "answer": 14153
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7098128734 and 2073486768?",
    "answer": 9171615502
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2 and 3?",
    "answer": 5
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1548289515 and 8527418982?",
    "answer": 10075708497
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2565935095 and 3143924172?",
    "answer": 5709859267
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7 and 7?",
    "answer": 14
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 561 and 205?",
    "answer": 766
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3713 and 6421?",
    "answer": 10134
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 539718793 and 993501213?",
    "answer": 1533220006
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3730 and 3402?",
    "answer": 7132
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 269 and 904?",
    "answer": 1173
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4 and 2?",
    "answer": 6
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 407398998 and 990114533?",
    "answer": 1397513531
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 907 and 692?",
    "answer": 1599
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 93 and 76?",
    "answer": 169
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 25346 and 59229?",
    "answer": 84575
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 90411882 and 12228821?",
    "answer": 102640703
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 448939277 and 101368864?",
    "answer": 550308141
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 93 and 97?",
    "answer": 190
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6 and 9?",
    "answer": 15
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 84954256 and 28301717?",
    "answer": 113255973
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 850 and 528?",
    "answer": 1378
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9 and 5?",
    "answer": 14
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 170744 and 944170?",
    "answer": 1114914
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3315733654 and 9391449014?",
    "answer": 12707182668
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4900926945 and 6931322851?",
    "answer": 11832249796
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 775 and 252?",
    "answer": 1027
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6734143284 and 8108848988?",
    "answer": 14842992272
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4835 and 8247?",
    "answer": 13082
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 91490332 and 37136972?",
    "answer": 128627304
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 81495 and 92745?",
    "answer": 174240
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 344600887 and 304168108?",
    "answer": 648768995
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6260306182 and 6885738459?",
    "answer": 13146044641
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 38725 and 39567?",
    "answer": 78292
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7817656772 and 8528375061?",
    "answer": 16346031833
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5040600 and 7126550?",
    "answer": 12167150
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1880144 and 1791482?",
    "answer": 3671626
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 73911443 and 74773491?",
    "answer": 148684934
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 784508177 and 787834268?",
    "answer": 1572342445
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6098911373 and 7373518097?",
    "answer": 13472429470
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2 and 8?",
    "answer": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 51 and 85?",
    "answer": 136
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 66 and 82?",
    "answer": 148
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 68198470 and 51734382?",
    "answer": 119932852
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6253289731 and 1498201336?",
    "answer": 7751491067
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 94137727 and 22124366?",
    "answer": 116262093
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 183277496 and 246069398?",
    "answer": 429346894
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 38 and 88?",
    "answer": 126
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 177087 and 452833?",
    "answer": 629920
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 526689983 and 853981353?",
    "answer": 1380671336
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 510402 and 410008?",
    "answer": 920410
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 628 and 823?",
    "answer": 1451
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 438344 and 937272?",
    "answer": 1375616
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4214980482 and 5119776077?",
    "answer": 9334756559
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 17063 and 83299?",
    "answer": 100362
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9639848 and 2208420?",
    "answer": 11848268
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7363005 and 3968101?",
    "answer": 11331106
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 80481369 and 37807040?",
    "answer": 118288409
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 571949603 and 890568066?",
    "answer": 1462517669
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 35 and 47?",
    "answer": 82
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8880 and 9391?",
    "answer": 18271
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 50668 and 70630?",
    "answer": 121298
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 943465818 and 495383135?",
    "answer": 1438848953
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 29856 and 75049?",
    "answer": 104905
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 25 and 66?",
    "answer": 91
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 98571711 and 60285069?",
    "answer": 158856780
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9 and 9?",
    "answer": 18
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 19743256 and 51916608?",
    "answer": 71659864
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 889029 and 901020?",
    "answer": 1790049
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9025 and 6212?",
    "answer": 15237
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 22619725 and 56310648?",
    "answer": 78930373
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5487 and 6465?",
    "answer": 11952
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7 and 4?",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 971242 and 964544?",
    "answer": 1935786
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 89643 and 65931?",
    "answer": 155574
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 46062641 and 82925264?",
    "answer": 128987905
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 51 and 92?",
    "answer": 143
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 67694 and 85273?",
    "answer": 152967
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4151222 and 1387229?",
    "answer": 5538451
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 30541 and 38267?",
    "answer": 68808
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 337164390 and 781866023?",
    "answer": 1119030413
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 482428 and 444535?",
    "answer": 926963
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2987045 and 2848159?",
    "answer": 5835204
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 859946349 and 471083140?",
    "answer": 1331029489
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 48066 and 61838?",
    "answer": 109904
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 18484690 and 61070554?",
    "answer": 79555244
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 67632376 and 29413113?",
    "answer": 97045489
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 57 and 96?",
    "answer": 153
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 93 and 82?",
    "answer": 175
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 269 and 634?",
    "answer": 903
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 20981874 and 58814053?",
    "answer": 79795927
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8234580188 and 1167662084?",
    "answer": 9402242272
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1141206 and 9213017?",
    "answer": 10354223
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 432534 and 891276?",
    "answer": 1323810
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4913509 and 4683698?",
    "answer": 9597207
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 64067 and 78098?",
    "answer": 142165
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 67 and 12?",
    "answer": 79
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 47 and 47?",
    "answer": 94
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 492614186 and 742766561?",
    "answer": 1235380747
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 276466 and 762131?",
    "answer": 1038597
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 24 and 16?",
    "answer": 40
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6865 and 4957?",
    "answer": 11822
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 78563 and 98673?",
    "answer": 177236
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6 and 5?",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 447 and 710?",
    "answer": 1157
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 85 and 79?",
    "answer": 164
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7324 and 2220?",
    "answer": 9544
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3507 and 5965?",
    "answer": 9472
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6623625 and 9766844?",
    "answer": 16390469
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2 and 8?",
    "answer": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1994932313 and 3017532310?",
    "answer": 5012464623
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1348662080 and 6712463189?",
    "answer": 8061125269
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 134745522 and 427465072?",
    "answer": 562210594
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9118330 and 4183405?",
    "answer": 13301735
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 82997179 and 58637493?",
    "answer": 141634672
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5788 and 8061?",
    "answer": 13849
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 67939 and 57514?",
    "answer": 125453
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1 and 3?",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1454234 and 6125351?",
    "answer": 7579585
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9230301 and 9441223?",
    "answer": 18671524
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 25 and 50?",
    "answer": 75
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 357 and 714?",
    "answer": 1071
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1486880 and 2640303?",
    "answer": 4127183
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 997062400 and 975225301?",
    "answer": 1972287701
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 627 and 654?",
    "answer": 1281
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3 and 8?",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 13 and 10?",
    "answer": 23
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 13 and 21?",
    "answer": 34
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3732 and 5812?",
    "answer": 9544
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7960295 and 5499553?",
    "answer": 13459848
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4711859 and 4804208?",
    "answer": 9516067
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 351024265 and 677412672?",
    "answer": 1028436937
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 940762966 and 597410858?",
    "answer": 1538173824
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1028 and 7951?",
    "answer": 8979
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5283189039 and 9224192753?",
    "answer": 14507381792
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 669641068 and 239483425?",
    "answer": 909124493
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 48 and 29?",
    "answer": 77
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7562501229 and 4098078068?",
    "answer": 11660579297
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 977068 and 696404?",
    "answer": 1673472
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 56732 and 21473?",
    "answer": 78205
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4638102 and 8118266?",
    "answer": 12756368
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 74 and 39?",
    "answer": 113
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 705573082 and 137982976?",
    "answer": 843556058
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 71838 and 87107?",
    "answer": 158945
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 27413 and 83616?",
    "answer": 111029
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 279 and 344?",
    "answer": 623
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 582804 and 718420?",
    "answer": 1301224
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 12 and 16?",
    "answer": 28
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3617361410 and 7108265380?",
    "answer": 10725626790
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 74514601 and 13305414?",
    "answer": 87820015
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3615667415 and 5323690134?",
    "answer": 8939357549
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1731235 and 1307103?",
    "answer": 3038338
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1567286239 and 3555728467?",
    "answer": 5123014706
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 73049281 and 55789927?",
    "answer": 128839208
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3131 and 9188?",
    "answer": 12319
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 501246074 and 328173608?",
    "answer": 829419682
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1339546 and 7301938?",
    "answer": 8641484
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 28798 and 20088?",
    "answer": 48886
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8 and 5?",
    "answer": 13
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5459682 and 4391231?",
    "answer": 9850913
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7165976748 and 1820954159?",
    "answer": 8986930907
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 493817546 and 967237090?",
    "answer": 1461054636
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1 and 9?",
    "answer": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6437449516 and 7169808445?",
    "answer": 13607257961
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 76 and 89?",
    "answer": 165
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8 and 6?",
    "answer": 14
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2 and 6?",
    "answer": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 790603805 and 163905071?",
    "answer": 954508876
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9349055621 and 5954364308?",
    "answer": 15303419929
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3397951 and 5534342?",
    "answer": 8932293
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 75569 and 82997?",
    "answer": 158566
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4 and 9?",
    "answer": 13
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1507 and 9348?",
    "answer": 10855
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 12233 and 88221?",
    "answer": 100454
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 65704 and 86006?",
    "answer": 151710
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7895 and 8870?",
    "answer": 16765
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 58417254 and 82575101?",
    "answer": 140992355
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5 and 6?",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 29 and 12?",
    "answer": 41
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 54876 and 67115?",
    "answer": 121991
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 15 and 38?",
    "answer": 53
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 990589409 and 140226687?",
    "answer": 1130816096
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 81626665 and 38722834?",
    "answer": 120349499
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 622 and 221?",
    "answer": 843
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7879 and 7542?",
    "answer": 15421
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6161913890 and 6675545930?",
    "answer": 12837459820
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6942 and 1988?",
    "answer": 8930
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 318 and 158?",
    "answer": 476
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5460 and 2533?",
    "answer": 7993
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6062453 and 1630864?",
    "answer": 7693317
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 116346010 and 150968047?",
    "answer": 267314057
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 250303511 and 297247135?",
    "answer": 547550646
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 914 and 325?",
    "answer": 1239
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7316683 and 3256699?",
    "answer": 10573382
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7903432059 and 8718004902?",
    "answer": 16621436961
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 941603 and 614932?",
    "answer": 1556535
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1814 and 9258?",
    "answer": 11072
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 918 and 372?",
    "answer": 1290
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 76945504 and 48255708?",
    "answer": 125201212
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7805086637 and 3209961968?",
    "answer": 11015048605
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3725 and 8006?",
    "answer": 11731
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 996808790 and 916683699?",
    "answer": 1913492489
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 79 and 58?",
    "answer": 137
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7524860764 and 2463705657?",
    "answer": 9988566421
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4486340297 and 3228020332?",
    "answer": 7714360629
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 92 and 12?",
    "answer": 104
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 278949967 and 953241362?",
    "answer": 1232191329
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1 and 7?",
    "answer": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 76603 and 61970?",
    "answer": 138573
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3671768 and 4864054?",
    "answer": 8535822
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 359 and 664?",
    "answer": 1023
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9508969 and 5261260?",
    "answer": 14770229
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 48510269 and 17805287?",
    "answer": 66315556
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2443392 and 3212441?",
    "answer": 5655833
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 29925 and 89065?",
    "answer": 118990
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4212 and 1944?",
    "answer": 6156
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3 and 3?",
    "answer": 6
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8 and 8?",
    "answer": 16
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5 and 6?",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 142525044 and 514633950?",
    "answer": 657158994
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 574581141 and 223248595?",
    "answer": 797829736
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 714 and 653?",
    "answer": 1367
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 264194284 and 334867625?",
    "answer": 599061909
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 619056 and 499085?",
    "answer": 1118141
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6087670 and 9935740?",
    "answer": 16023410
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 30934 and 81751?",
    "answer": 112685
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 317303002 and 153815416?",
    "answer": 471118418
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6387 and 5668?",
    "answer": 12055
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2 and 2?",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5118009 and 9939337?",
    "answer": 15057346
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 36474837 and 31570736?",
    "answer": 68045573
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9709 and 3641?",
    "answer": 13350
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 22 and 36?",
    "answer": 58
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 934118402 and 973990004?",
    "answer": 1908108406
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 875865 and 865973?",
    "answer": 1741838
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 891 and 941?",
    "answer": 1832
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 44711 and 33930?",
    "answer": 78641
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3600 and 7427?",
    "answer": 11027
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4 and 9?",
    "answer": 13
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 94411086 and 47489665?",
    "answer": 141900751
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4 and 9?",
    "answer": 13
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 952081489 and 942782694?",
    "answer": 1894864183
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 793717458 and 890537205?",
    "answer": 1684254663
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 98179177 and 15371379?",
    "answer": 113550556
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 81805716 and 96162512?",
    "answer": 177968228
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 88 and 68?",
    "answer": 156
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 86369877 and 88070352?",
    "answer": 174440229
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3 and 1?",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1722113978 and 2735177736?",
    "answer": 4457291714
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 54 and 20?",
    "answer": 74
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 869672751 and 871740684?",
    "answer": 1741413435
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8 and 4?",
    "answer": 12
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7 and 6?",
    "answer": 13
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3386257082 and 1028187747?",
    "answer": 4414444829
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5 and 4?",
    "answer": 9
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 280 and 835?",
    "answer": 1115
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 265295 and 399646?",
    "answer": 664941
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 40389 and 51106?",
    "answer": 91495
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 506 and 592?",
    "answer": 1098
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 673 and 144?",
    "answer": 817
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 130 and 813?",
    "answer": 943
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 38 and 95?",
    "answer": 133
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 514904979 and 993951538?",
    "answer": 1508856517
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 58239 and 12418?",
    "answer": 70657
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9 and 5?",
    "answer": 14
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 33695 and 94648?",
    "answer": 128343
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 205903704 and 764655660?",
    "answer": 970559364
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5 and 6?",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 308321 and 657515?",
    "answer": 965836
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 220744545 and 399469407?",
    "answer": 620213952
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 39288 and 57963?",
    "answer": 97251
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4263079645 and 7573201017?",
    "answer": 11836280662
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8334239401 and 7219413365?",
    "answer": 15553652766
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 744514077 and 738944213?",
    "answer": 1483458290
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5844 and 2462?",
    "answer": 8306
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 66096 and 87949?",
    "answer": 154045
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 73578 and 76052?",
    "answer": 149630
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 50 and 64?",
    "answer": 114
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 51729 and 31189?",
    "answer": 82918
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9329 and 8224?",
    "answer": 17553
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1811097 and 5114319?",
    "answer": 6925416
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 23 and 59?",
    "answer": 82
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 249570322 and 924913665?",
    "answer": 1174483987
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 95679007 and 42297330?",
    "answer": 137976337
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 667 and 676?",
    "answer": 1343
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2936066 and 9591977?",
    "answer": 12528043
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 854320 and 163449?",
    "answer": 1017769
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 68738 and 33011?",
    "answer": 101749
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 988827 and 706592?",
    "answer": 1695419
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2 and 8?",
    "answer": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3253541979 and 5547343180?",
    "answer": 8800885159
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 25207 and 94769?",
    "answer": 119976
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 732355 and 573286?",
    "answer": 1305641
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9 and 1?",
    "answer": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 257243183 and 314498497?",
    "answer": 571741680
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 133831 and 797942?",
    "answer": 931773
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 556 and 507?",
    "answer": 1063
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 825 and 582?",
    "answer": 1407
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 322859993 and 748222694?",
    "answer": 1071082687
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9933 and 3171?",
    "answer": 13104
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 552664 and 361917?",
    "answer": 914581
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 478 and 446?",
    "answer": 924
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 84219 and 64304?",
    "answer": 148523
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8740 and 7363?",
    "answer": 16103
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2661 and 1567?",
    "answer": 4228
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 896028426 and 507048017?",
    "answer": 1403076443
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9218244947 and 4860021195?",
    "answer": 14078266142
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 298 and 174?",
    "answer": 472
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 498467222 and 372262927?",
    "answer": 870730149
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2592 and 1709?",
    "answer": 4301
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 583510 and 792068?",
    "answer": 1375578
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 28 and 13?",
    "answer": 41
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 931847 and 243251?",
    "answer": 1175098
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9840 and 1824?",
    "answer": 11664
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 506319 and 896295?",
    "answer": 1402614
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 231385 and 358083?",
    "answer": 589468
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 526 and 764?",
    "answer": 1290
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 888 and 119?",
    "answer": 1007
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 60326976 and 62921636?",
    "answer": 123248612
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 99252 and 55720?",
    "answer": 154972
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3628671 and 2017172?",
    "answer": 5645843
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 915 and 103?",
    "answer": 1018
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 46314839 and 27563556?",
    "answer": 73878395
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 649715 and 668591?",
    "answer": 1318306
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4507898 and 5042925?",
    "answer": 9550823
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 42 and 53?",
    "answer": 95
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 64934429 and 74983989?",
    "answer": 139918418
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8583814155 and 3812063470?",
    "answer": 12395877625
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1676 and 5416?",
    "answer": 7092
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 221382309 and 131558840?",
    "answer": 352941149
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 477984 and 648956?",
    "answer": 1126940
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 31179 and 60773?",
    "answer": 91952
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 87227410 and 60504346?",
    "answer": 147731756
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2297 and 8883?",
    "answer": 11180
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7144356843 and 9238537145?",
    "answer": 16382893988
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 12 and 32?",
    "answer": 44
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9174560 and 1110492?",
    "answer": 10285052
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 362201 and 449846?",
    "answer": 812047
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 744707 and 399321?",
    "answer": 1144028
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5 and 8?",
    "answer": 13
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2 and 6?",
    "answer": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 29143059 and 84239635?",
    "answer": 113382694
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 67 and 98?",
    "answer": 165
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 42893952 and 29206937?",
    "answer": 72100889
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 16464036 and 15310939?",
    "answer": 31774975
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 326409 and 454639?",
    "answer": 781048
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 28 and 55?",
    "answer": 83
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 93655 and 17613?",
    "answer": 111268
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 25792 and 39074?",
    "answer": 64866
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6751008360 and 2978972908?",
    "answer": 9729981268
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1696534531 and 2813669634?",
    "answer": 4510204165
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7186 and 2950?",
    "answer": 10136
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8071621769 and 1160275955?",
    "answer": 9231897724
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 40170509 and 64860824?",
    "answer": 105031333
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1 and 7?",
    "answer": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3401897802 and 5564999137?",
    "answer": 8966896939
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 314 and 524?",
    "answer": 838
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 138224 and 723566?",
    "answer": 861790
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 37218 and 33077?",
    "answer": 70295
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 29461468 and 14457404?",
    "answer": 43918872
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3345323419 and 1371166454?",
    "answer": 4716489873
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5237 and 7310?",
    "answer": 12547
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5 and 4?",
    "answer": 9
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 68131 and 38141?",
    "answer": 106272
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1405029456 and 9637465488?",
    "answer": 11042494944
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 66082 and 72288?",
    "answer": 138370
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 29 and 48?",
    "answer": 77
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2317131551 and 8330262213?",
    "answer": 10647393764
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 594666099 and 887684444?",
    "answer": 1482350543
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8585 and 4561?",
    "answer": 13146
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 846 and 596?",
    "answer": 1442
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 406 and 630?",
    "answer": 1036
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3404845 and 3838976?",
    "answer": 7243821
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 401314878 and 964947926?",
    "answer": 1366262804
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 19508 and 94321?",
    "answer": 113829
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 851707 and 201822?",
    "answer": 1053529
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 62436 and 20911?",
    "answer": 83347
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 915747 and 594438?",
    "answer": 1510185
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 36586897 and 35687321?",
    "answer": 72274218
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8175544174 and 8343980451?",
    "answer": 16519524625
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2205374601 and 7879386982?",
    "answer": 10084761583
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1250460093 and 7666493242?",
    "answer": 8916953335
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 56989104 and 23950030?",
    "answer": 80939134
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 375 and 361?",
    "answer": 736
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5076766606 and 6361057551?",
    "answer": 11437824157
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 451 and 594?",
    "answer": 1045
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8527 and 3770?",
    "answer": 12297
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 82583057 and 41153093?",
    "answer": 123736150
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5055 and 3218?",
    "answer": 8273
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2 and 2?",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 64564022 and 63830864?",
    "answer": 128394886
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 54923 and 83141?",
    "answer": 138064
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9 and 1?",
    "answer": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 986144 and 825223?",
    "answer": 1811367
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4573721699 and 3756989765?",
    "answer": 8330711464
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 796697691 and 547958031?",
    "answer": 1344655722
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 263 and 630?",
    "answer": 893
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 392698884 and 747678152?",
    "answer": 1140377036
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 492465989 and 935677441?",
    "answer": 1428143430
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 91393563 and 57634772?",
    "answer": 149028335
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9 and 1?",
    "answer": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9754406 and 4828365?",
    "answer": 14582771
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6 and 2?",
    "answer": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3693393 and 4993867?",
    "answer": 8687260
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5093570 and 8516946?",
    "answer": 13610516
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 831566190 and 351335873?",
    "answer": 1182902063
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 78869 and 40704?",
    "answer": 119573
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 424087059 and 604938313?",
    "answer": 1029025372
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 90 and 42?",
    "answer": 132
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3276018 and 6946465?",
    "answer": 10222483
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 67 and 46?",
    "answer": 113
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7013 and 7056?",
    "answer": 14069
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 242867 and 337970?",
    "answer": 580837
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 65950713 and 21638542?",
    "answer": 87589255
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1 and 2?",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 11 and 17?",
    "answer": 28
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 430409719 and 446650278?",
    "answer": 877059997
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 30888353 and 32446286?",
    "answer": 63334639
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 41705 and 51601?",
    "answer": 93306
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6 and 2?",
    "answer": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8201 and 7399?",
    "answer": 15600
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1557552 and 8768762?",
    "answer": 10326314
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4737384849 and 8219168158?",
    "answer": 12956553007
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 84 and 72?",
    "answer": 156
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 81338 and 93875?",
    "answer": 175213
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3 and 3?",
    "answer": 6
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2 and 4?",
    "answer": 6
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4680885 and 2962537?",
    "answer": 7643422
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 752401 and 560398?",
    "answer": 1312799
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3 and 4?",
    "answer": 7
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 42975 and 36941?",
    "answer": 79916
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 83 and 60?",
    "answer": 143
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4314 and 1827?",
    "answer": 6141
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 32 and 45?",
    "answer": 77
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 39067 and 10671?",
    "answer": 49738
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 961 and 412?",
    "answer": 1373
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7296281384 and 9963931336?",
    "answer": 17260212720
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 88426 and 78655?",
    "answer": 167081
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 82551 and 12990?",
    "answer": 95541
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7509142 and 8677639?",
    "answer": 16186781
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 948723 and 157925?",
    "answer": 1106648
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 93933511 and 81166892?",
    "answer": 175100403
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8434983655 and 9554551065?",
    "answer": 17989534720
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3 and 6?",
    "answer": 9
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 477 and 794?",
    "answer": 1271
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 415044634 and 146660882?",
    "answer": 561705516
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 49007810 and 36024925?",
    "answer": 85032735
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 470 and 831?",
    "answer": 1301
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 64722800 and 67206684?",
    "answer": 131929484
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4 and 3?",
    "answer": 7
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6 and 6?",
    "answer": 12
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4749053 and 9956883?",
    "answer": 14705936
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 740 and 371?",
    "answer": 1111
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7 and 4?",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 80432961 and 98499568?",
    "answer": 178932529
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3568888142 and 1616368184?",
    "answer": 5185256326
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3788208 and 9436581?",
    "answer": 13224789
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2712418 and 5169352?",
    "answer": 7881770
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 757 and 145?",
    "answer": 902
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 50 and 96?",
    "answer": 146
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 20384 and 48260?",
    "answer": 68644
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7294258 and 7768469?",
    "answer": 15062727
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7290543052 and 2839208713?",
    "answer": 10129751765
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 96484 and 64438?",
    "answer": 160922
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 62613731 and 44527956?",
    "answer": 107141687
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 289570556 and 266130881?",
    "answer": 555701437
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 53 and 19?",
    "answer": 72
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 33 and 62?",
    "answer": 95
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8347656426 and 1597755004?",
    "answer": 9945411430
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 63 and 43?",
    "answer": 106
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 504 and 101?",
    "answer": 605
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 20 and 84?",
    "answer": 104
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3894155 and 1750852?",
    "answer": 5645007
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 56828848 and 41882155?",
    "answer": 98711003
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1 and 3?",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6771 and 5573?",
    "answer": 12344
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 160313 and 288537?",
    "answer": 448850
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 40857914 and 80386451?",
    "answer": 121244365
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4 and 8?",
    "answer": 12
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 34816 and 76707?",
    "answer": 111523
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5090401425 and 8575281328?",
    "answer": 13665682753
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8448 and 1158?",
    "answer": 9606
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4 and 6?",
    "answer": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5622 and 5352?",
    "answer": 10974
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6042 and 5358?",
    "answer": 11400
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2660866565 and 7352113432?",
    "answer": 10012979997
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2088773864 and 7038213263?",
    "answer": 9126987127
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4241131910 and 8994398231?",
    "answer": 13235530141
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 366235 and 999783?",
    "answer": 1366018
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 826859 and 137010?",
    "answer": 963869
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 65 and 59?",
    "answer": 124
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 713 and 725?",
    "answer": 1438
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6691783515 and 5445637835?",
    "answer": 12137421350
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 24587171 and 98343044?",
    "answer": 122930215
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 360870051 and 434275676?",
    "answer": 795145727
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6524613 and 6237485?",
    "answer": 12762098
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6427469 and 1936039?",
    "answer": 8363508
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4612236922 and 4700486334?",
    "answer": 9312723256
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 20383 and 76486?",
    "answer": 96869
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 52 and 51?",
    "answer": 103
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 281133 and 814783?",
    "answer": 1095916
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 54019 and 30040?",
    "answer": 84059
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9973004819 and 5812964814?",
    "answer": 15785969633
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1055899 and 6369141?",
    "answer": 7425040
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8149129 and 3631721?",
    "answer": 11780850
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 86654 and 20132?",
    "answer": 106786
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2090025412 and 7507659297?",
    "answer": 9597684709
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 543 and 132?",
    "answer": 675
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 39798 and 66367?",
    "answer": 106165
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 40312 and 52984?",
    "answer": 93296
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8765068 and 2461661?",
    "answer": 11226729
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7544795 and 4186978?",
    "answer": 11731773
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 119696110 and 735106423?",
    "answer": 854802533
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 83 and 87?",
    "answer": 170
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4 and 9?",
    "answer": 13
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 102 and 709?",
    "answer": 811
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 74468132 and 81694804?",
    "answer": 156162936
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 62745 and 51849?",
    "answer": 114594
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4 and 1?",
    "answer": 5
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 611 and 313?",
    "answer": 924
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3249 and 7546?",
    "answer": 10795
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2954011821 and 6170954999?",
    "answer": 9124966820
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 837 and 456?",
    "answer": 1293
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4054144041 and 3373719239?",
    "answer": 7427863280
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 68 and 13?",
    "answer": 81
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4717 and 9916?",
    "answer": 14633
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6500690068 and 9864429461?",
    "answer": 16365119529
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 48 and 99?",
    "answer": 147
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 589678 and 247565?",
    "answer": 837243
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 50 and 59?",
    "answer": 109
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2 and 3?",
    "answer": 5
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 33853 and 74301?",
    "answer": 108154
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 923 and 758?",
    "answer": 1681
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 32992606 and 95295134?",
    "answer": 128287740
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6548851 and 4671820?",
    "answer": 11220671
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5305 and 1892?",
    "answer": 7197
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1 and 5?",
    "answer": 6
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5 and 1?",
    "answer": 6
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 60 and 28?",
    "answer": 88
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9730677 and 6816349?",
    "answer": 16547026
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 605624 and 799112?",
    "answer": 1404736
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4963922386 and 1621928602?",
    "answer": 6585850988
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1664842 and 9655685?",
    "answer": 11320527
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 455 and 759?",
    "answer": 1214
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2763416745 and 1902153253?",
    "answer": 4665569998
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 17087 and 58467?",
    "answer": 75554
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 220765 and 720637?",
    "answer": 941402
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 40301488 and 48381159?",
    "answer": 88682647
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 51693 and 64215?",
    "answer": 115908
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 29919 and 68103?",
    "answer": 98022
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7 and 1?",
    "answer": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9914 and 1571?",
    "answer": 11485
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1 and 9?",
    "answer": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8694839 and 6821054?",
    "answer": 15515893
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 49857 and 24272?",
    "answer": 74129
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 20458 and 59466?",
    "answer": 79924
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6649359 and 4917754?",
    "answer": 11567113
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 52 and 50?",
    "answer": 102
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 43 and 25?",
    "answer": 68
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9815348941 and 6323403542?",
    "answer": 16138752483
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4983188332 and 2380516609?",
    "answer": 7363704941
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7390 and 4605?",
    "answer": 11995
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7 and 4?",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 837 and 432?",
    "answer": 1269
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 77 and 23?",
    "answer": 100
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 88738 and 45447?",
    "answer": 134185
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 85345 and 18161?",
    "answer": 103506
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 748 and 747?",
    "answer": 1495
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 55772 and 55795?",
    "answer": 111567
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8478199 and 1314820?",
    "answer": 9793019
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 45265268 and 29622940?",
    "answer": 74888208
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 10879 and 33974?",
    "answer": 44853
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 646708540 and 634969316?",
    "answer": 1281677856
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 964034479 and 433345038?",
    "answer": 1397379517
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 68379486 and 34239615?",
    "answer": 102619101
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1891 and 1608?",
    "answer": 3499
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4602717001 and 7155702178?",
    "answer": 11758419179
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 68973052 and 52696680?",
    "answer": 121669732
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 359544250 and 375061410?",
    "answer": 734605660
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4 and 3?",
    "answer": 7
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6993111071 and 9135279249?",
    "answer": 16128390320
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 57 and 53?",
    "answer": 110
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 508029 and 306970?",
    "answer": 814999
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 432 and 568?",
    "answer": 1000
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 686665548 and 242892860?",
    "answer": 929558408
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 66001 and 74007?",
    "answer": 140008
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3 and 9?",
    "answer": 12
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 21458 and 76416?",
    "answer": 97874
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5915 and 5495?",
    "answer": 11410
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7602509 and 2434504?",
    "answer": 10037013
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8606379 and 5259289?",
    "answer": 13865668
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 457464 and 961637?",
    "answer": 1419101
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9049636015 and 5954123227?",
    "answer": 15003759242
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 43625668 and 30043003?",
    "answer": 73668671
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 62473176 and 97961595?",
    "answer": 160434771
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5874 and 4032?",
    "answer": 9906
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8196890281 and 5418575391?",
    "answer": 13615465672
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 256 and 865?",
    "answer": 1121
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 447907822 and 364289934?",
    "answer": 812197756
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 799989 and 264082?",
    "answer": 1064071
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8185 and 7258?",
    "answer": 15443
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 554348 and 320119?",
    "answer": 874467
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7 and 7?",
    "answer": 14
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 58 and 29?",
    "answer": 87
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7024742068 and 7511201032?",
    "answer": 14535943100
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4041022520 and 5510710084?",
    "answer": 9551732604
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6091583272 and 3772797594?",
    "answer": 9864380866
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 762 and 594?",
    "answer": 1356
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2092605004 and 9457071390?",
    "answer": 11549676394
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 721 and 136?",
    "answer": 857
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 369 and 929?",
    "answer": 1298
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8725 and 1865?",
    "answer": 10590
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8649 and 4116?",
    "answer": 12765
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2061 and 9310?",
    "answer": 11371
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8453304650 and 2707728843?",
    "answer": 11161033493
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 83604 and 49878?",
    "answer": 133482
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6 and 3?",
    "answer": 9
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 53 and 37?",
    "answer": 90
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 69859443 and 76102625?",
    "answer": 145962068
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5388 and 4069?",
    "answer": 9457
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2440269 and 7025892?",
    "answer": 9466161
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 434965924 and 218778019?",
    "answer": 653743943
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 588 and 302?",
    "answer": 890
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2987 and 3377?",
    "answer": 6364
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 558149 and 939477?",
    "answer": 1497626
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 22760185 and 62016417?",
    "answer": 84776602
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 32454447 and 47853392?",
    "answer": 80307839
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8573 and 9337?",
    "answer": 17910
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 72 and 25?",
    "answer": 97
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2091793 and 1736546?",
    "answer": 3828339
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7073137065 and 7710193444?",
    "answer": 14783330509
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4959 and 5616?",
    "answer": 10575
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 16 and 80?",
    "answer": 96
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 15 and 56?",
    "answer": 71
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6807196 and 8394030?",
    "answer": 15201226
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6 and 1?",
    "answer": 7
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 544 and 152?",
    "answer": 696
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 969720 and 598760?",
    "answer": 1568480
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1232576618 and 4030975699?",
    "answer": 5263552317
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7649413 and 7704238?",
    "answer": 15353651
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9596291 and 7902317?",
    "answer": 17498608
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1634 and 8687?",
    "answer": 10321
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9541 and 7073?",
    "answer": 16614
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 92156005 and 90743826?",
    "answer": 182899831
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1 and 3?",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 782075881 and 835635078?",
    "answer": 1617710959
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 873461638 and 259863481?",
    "answer": 1133325119
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4101688285 and 4704565370?",
    "answer": 8806253655
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 18336 and 57129?",
    "answer": 75465
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3277791 and 6090845?",
    "answer": 9368636
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 46564839 and 99986074?",
    "answer": 146550913
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 843767 and 937700?",
    "answer": 1781467
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 57096257 and 45202593?",
    "answer": 102298850
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 56 and 82?",
    "answer": 138
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 632 and 849?",
    "answer": 1481
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5 and 7?",
    "answer": 12
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 280 and 114?",
    "answer": 394
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6811 and 6285?",
    "answer": 13096
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 511211 and 891877?",
    "answer": 1403088
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 960043 and 205741?",
    "answer": 1165784
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 59602598 and 54568479?",
    "answer": 114171077
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 99 and 46?",
    "answer": 145
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2140634899 and 3634775678?",
    "answer": 5775410577
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 93935 and 40256?",
    "answer": 134191
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8493831160 and 5890459670?",
    "answer": 14384290830
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 772 and 214?",
    "answer": 986
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4500646 and 2975867?",
    "answer": 7476513
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 618014 and 321200?",
    "answer": 939214
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 21744677 and 53929548?",
    "answer": 75674225
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 34 and 14?",
    "answer": 48
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 753 and 294?",
    "answer": 1047
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6475263815 and 1289480498?",
    "answer": 7764744313
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 119717357 and 918692867?",
    "answer": 1038410224
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6071835959 and 9848115849?",
    "answer": 15919951808
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2616 and 8621?",
    "answer": 11237
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 295 and 110?",
    "answer": 405
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5323628 and 9024363?",
    "answer": 14347991
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 31050310 and 50672955?",
    "answer": 81723265
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3 and 3?",
    "answer": 6
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8328213775 and 8093309259?",
    "answer": 16421523034
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2846774339 and 5508561239?",
    "answer": 8355335578
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 57393 and 36818?",
    "answer": 94211
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 127251 and 313102?",
    "answer": 440353
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3068 and 9445?",
    "answer": 12513
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 54 and 49?",
    "answer": 103
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 48 and 25?",
    "answer": 73
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 846070850 and 580131273?",
    "answer": 1426202123
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 50496559 and 67368788?",
    "answer": 117865347
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7824785 and 3735990?",
    "answer": 11560775
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 241274931 and 175292630?",
    "answer": 416567561
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9467283 and 3079612?",
    "answer": 12546895
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 168 and 928?",
    "answer": 1096
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7525 and 2863?",
    "answer": 10388
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 92269533 and 65416350?",
    "answer": 157685883
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 370 and 870?",
    "answer": 1240
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 911 and 530?",
    "answer": 1441
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9048314760 and 1056805883?",
    "answer": 10105120643
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9 and 6?",
    "answer": 15
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 762797482 and 993075005?",
    "answer": 1755872487
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8463467477 and 2678847950?",
    "answer": 11142315427
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 337 and 298?",
    "answer": 635
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 34 and 76?",
    "answer": 110
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 23019 and 32043?",
    "answer": 55062
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3480615 and 8132123?",
    "answer": 11612738
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 15920530 and 59578910?",
    "answer": 75499440
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 602027 and 495178?",
    "answer": 1097205
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9605493023 and 5893692542?",
    "answer": 15499185565
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 940475427 and 917618762?",
    "answer": 1858094189
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5905725 and 8069146?",
    "answer": 13974871
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 64106635 and 30564031?",
    "answer": 94670666
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 54040 and 41540?",
    "answer": 95580
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 925390 and 760033?",
    "answer": 1685423
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 67558 and 58857?",
    "answer": 126415
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 52521616 and 53867054?",
    "answer": 106388670
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 728876225 and 632585737?",
    "answer": 1361461962
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 341597154 and 862493247?",
    "answer": 1204090401
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 160 and 433?",
    "answer": 593
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3281866 and 9793280?",
    "answer": 13075146
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7 and 8?",
    "answer": 15
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 69 and 43?",
    "answer": 112
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5946553 and 2415710?",
    "answer": 8362263
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 288357 and 128103?",
    "answer": 416460
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 45941180 and 92787314?",
    "answer": 138728494
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 20 and 29?",
    "answer": 49
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2326 and 1566?",
    "answer": 3892
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 17578 and 50179?",
    "answer": 67757
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 30 and 62?",
    "answer": 92
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1801 and 6726?",
    "answer": 8527
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 85 and 16?",
    "answer": 101
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 91229903 and 45587948?",
    "answer": 136817851
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4 and 8?",
    "answer": 12
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 575656004 and 108408987?",
    "answer": 684064991
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 994172283 and 574027980?",
    "answer": 1568200263
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 875 and 573?",
    "answer": 1448
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 611736 and 181916?",
    "answer": 793652
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9362013 and 5917271?",
    "answer": 15279284
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4 and 4?",
    "answer": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 409 and 428?",
    "answer": 837
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 570669 and 517527?",
    "answer": 1088196
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1946 and 7980?",
    "answer": 9926
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 34003 and 23739?",
    "answer": 57742
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7293902309 and 9305261928?",
    "answer": 16599164237
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3056 and 3961?",
    "answer": 7017
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 74509 and 34616?",
    "answer": 109125
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 93176 and 34876?",
    "answer": 128052
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7 and 7?",
    "answer": 14
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1 and 7?",
    "answer": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4331237 and 1133895?",
    "answer": 5465132
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 708240677 and 592404188?",
    "answer": 1300644865
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9 and 5?",
    "answer": 14
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8 and 3?",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 213 and 898?",
    "answer": 1111
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 863 and 126?",
    "answer": 989
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 668 and 692?",
    "answer": 1360
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1044449 and 9171575?",
    "answer": 10216024
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 492 and 928?",
    "answer": 1420
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 357501451 and 221637703?",
    "answer": 579139154
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 21145 and 62196?",
    "answer": 83341
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 685635 and 713461?",
    "answer": 1399096
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3 and 3?",
    "answer": 6
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 989 and 842?",
    "answer": 1831
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 16 and 93?",
    "answer": 109
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 40147423 and 68968825?",
    "answer": 109116248
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9109 and 2240?",
    "answer": 11349
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 32889 and 80680?",
    "answer": 113569
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1 and 2?",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 880732 and 821222?",
    "answer": 1701954
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2234138804 and 8743656948?",
    "answer": 10977795752
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 25099 and 66344?",
    "answer": 91443
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1215947273 and 8893656162?",
    "answer": 10109603435
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 840 and 537?",
    "answer": 1377
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4799848 and 5567869?",
    "answer": 10367717
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6489507336 and 7843196115?",
    "answer": 14332703451
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 127 and 239?",
    "answer": 366
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 963198504 and 839738511?",
    "answer": 1802937015
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 52 and 74?",
    "answer": 126
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4903841 and 2870551?",
    "answer": 7774392
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 197980170 and 926329144?",
    "answer": 1124309314
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8459679 and 1936572?",
    "answer": 10396251
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 887610 and 124005?",
    "answer": 1011615
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 79994 and 32327?",
    "answer": 112321
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6654100978 and 6007177478?",
    "answer": 12661278456
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 34846491 and 51697820?",
    "answer": 86544311
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9185 and 4986?",
    "answer": 14171
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 682823 and 297446?",
    "answer": 980269
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 956 and 366?",
    "answer": 1322
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 30890123 and 82967961?",
    "answer": 113858084
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1318899085 and 5982822695?",
    "answer": 7301721780
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4 and 7?",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5489 and 5370?",
    "answer": 10859
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 596279940 and 258849910?",
    "answer": 855129850
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 354 and 825?",
    "answer": 1179
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8773 and 1798?",
    "answer": 10571
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4586786352 and 1282259165?",
    "answer": 5869045517
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 77116848 and 76716575?",
    "answer": 153833423
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 70545 and 94643?",
    "answer": 165188
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 258 and 233?",
    "answer": 491
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 13357 and 23182?",
    "answer": 36539
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 590689088 and 438360709?",
    "answer": 1029049797
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7762 and 6460?",
    "answer": 14222
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 94950 and 90627?",
    "answer": 185577
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7480383 and 4064422?",
    "answer": 11544805
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 927210424 and 828952291?",
    "answer": 1756162715
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4 and 9?",
    "answer": 13
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5440 and 3453?",
    "answer": 8893
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 307770 and 333052?",
    "answer": 640822
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 19474 and 22591?",
    "answer": 42065
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7 and 6?",
    "answer": 13
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8917714751 and 5994315786?",
    "answer": 14912030537
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 56195183 and 35551138?",
    "answer": 91746321
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2826985 and 2828157?",
    "answer": 5655142
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 17455114 and 86352560?",
    "answer": 103807674
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4724212 and 7168543?",
    "answer": 11892755
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 454833 and 428707?",
    "answer": 883540
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7180 and 5871?",
    "answer": 13051
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8686446 and 2999363?",
    "answer": 11685809
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9580563123 and 6674855414?",
    "answer": 16255418537
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 49550 and 96730?",
    "answer": 146280
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8 and 1?",
    "answer": 9
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3623441717 and 5952336945?",
    "answer": 9575778662
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9492086716 and 2662752972?",
    "answer": 12154839688
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6162101 and 6731152?",
    "answer": 12893253
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 377 and 346?",
    "answer": 723
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 54932 and 73984?",
    "answer": 128916
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 65427 and 83401?",
    "answer": 148828
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8073688064 and 5927132764?",
    "answer": 14000820828
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 49746 and 31236?",
    "answer": 80982
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 940 and 518?",
    "answer": 1458
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1256122 and 2642519?",
    "answer": 3898641
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 640250 and 938526?",
    "answer": 1578776
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8 and 6?",
    "answer": 14
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 477 and 877?",
    "answer": 1354
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 97993264 and 88526540?",
    "answer": 186519804
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 35490 and 79304?",
    "answer": 114794
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 51 and 72?",
    "answer": 123
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 36263997 and 95379275?",
    "answer": 131643272
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9 and 4?",
    "answer": 13
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9009148 and 1318730?",
    "answer": 10327878
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 64 and 75?",
    "answer": 139
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1315702002 and 9168852609?",
    "answer": 10484554611
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7 and 7?",
    "answer": 14
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2543314 and 3803031?",
    "answer": 6346345
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9210850 and 9479223?",
    "answer": 18690073
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 684236860 and 148600520?",
    "answer": 832837380
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7 and 5?",
    "answer": 12
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 148772 and 473876?",
    "answer": 622648
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5 and 1?",
    "answer": 6
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5715992713 and 3296865905?",
    "answer": 9012858618
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 363278 and 423125?",
    "answer": 786403
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 789 and 622?",
    "answer": 1411
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3398517231 and 9137890373?",
    "answer": 12536407604
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 93 and 20?",
    "answer": 113
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 988249 and 998892?",
    "answer": 1987141
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 359 and 413?",
    "answer": 772
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7747825 and 4277272?",
    "answer": 12025097
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 73573631 and 90348232?",
    "answer": 163921863
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 43471 and 47573?",
    "answer": 91044
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 621 and 826?",
    "answer": 1447
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2860441 and 1427831?",
    "answer": 4288272
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 52757 and 49084?",
    "answer": 101841
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 82376488 and 42851436?",
    "answer": 125227924
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 45946 and 24529?",
    "answer": 70475
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 406 and 990?",
    "answer": 1396
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8282179 and 5079821?",
    "answer": 13362000
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 546805704 and 980851148?",
    "answer": 1527656852
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4 and 8?",
    "answer": 12
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 51063 and 99630?",
    "answer": 150693
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2580361769 and 1846582496?",
    "answer": 4426944265
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 708300 and 953726?",
    "answer": 1662026
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 879366 and 298404?",
    "answer": 1177770
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 57 and 68?",
    "answer": 125
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 758681 and 382509?",
    "answer": 1141190
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4591890448 and 7942234831?",
    "answer": 12534125279
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 990334 and 219351?",
    "answer": 1209685
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 724 and 568?",
    "answer": 1292
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 407 and 980?",
    "answer": 1387
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 392356 and 487925?",
    "answer": 880281
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 78 and 88?",
    "answer": 166
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 753933 and 238283?",
    "answer": 992216
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 88504 and 96184?",
    "answer": 184688
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 558108295 and 477203465?",
    "answer": 1035311760
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9584294096 and 1486925130?",
    "answer": 11071219226
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 200896989 and 949847980?",
    "answer": 1150744969
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1369 and 8078?",
    "answer": 9447
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2 and 3?",
    "answer": 5
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7 and 4?",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 17968167 and 16417600?",
    "answer": 34385767
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5777103 and 4210612?",
    "answer": 9987715
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 296756972 and 526077524?",
    "answer": 822834496
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 95296936 and 37751950?",
    "answer": 133048886
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 255341301 and 664998224?",
    "answer": 920339525
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5494280077 and 5887022485?",
    "answer": 11381302562
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 58280 and 91721?",
    "answer": 150001
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 390494675 and 733869937?",
    "answer": 1124364612
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1 and 1?",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2694258397 and 8636013521?",
    "answer": 11330271918
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 64512011 and 78934332?",
    "answer": 143446343
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 474665 and 937322?",
    "answer": 1411987
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4 and 4?",
    "answer": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 244613868 and 707254459?",
    "answer": 951868327
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4539672405 and 3739912041?",
    "answer": 8279584446
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7903867476 and 7658878341?",
    "answer": 15562745817
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 804367 and 552307?",
    "answer": 1356674
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 817390929 and 739913959?",
    "answer": 1557304888
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 16878383 and 76810422?",
    "answer": 93688805
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 81864 and 13999?",
    "answer": 95863
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8880 and 8000?",
    "answer": 16880
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 43226 and 96391?",
    "answer": 139617
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2 and 1?",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3 and 3?",
    "answer": 6
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7 and 7?",
    "answer": 14
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 203860 and 858650?",
    "answer": 1062510
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2 and 6?",
    "answer": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 32360908 and 12300177?",
    "answer": 44661085
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 497366854 and 488392341?",
    "answer": 985759195
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 829455 and 312507?",
    "answer": 1141962
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9087211806 and 3004839308?",
    "answer": 12092051114
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6744093 and 1775356?",
    "answer": 8519449
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 49 and 46?",
    "answer": 95
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 12176994 and 54609344?",
    "answer": 66786338
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2071161 and 8363036?",
    "answer": 10434197
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 18736299 and 79019822?",
    "answer": 97756121
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 459031565 and 997606747?",
    "answer": 1456638312
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 92901109 and 82651587?",
    "answer": 175552696
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7 and 4?",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 56329811 and 63141242?",
    "answer": 119471053
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 743677472 and 684217997?",
    "answer": 1427895469
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 43044 and 56132?",
    "answer": 99176
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4149064 and 3451122?",
    "answer": 7600186
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1324 and 1064?",
    "answer": 2388
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 56 and 46?",
    "answer": 102
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 89423735 and 19825627?",
    "answer": 109249362
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 962 and 186?",
    "answer": 1148
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 19 and 38?",
    "answer": 57
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 907 and 155?",
    "answer": 1062
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 554400 and 546077?",
    "answer": 1100477
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 66212 and 45674?",
    "answer": 111886
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 574361 and 102229?",
    "answer": 676590
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 946044 and 613029?",
    "answer": 1559073
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 617 and 513?",
    "answer": 1130
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3 and 4?",
    "answer": 7
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 35002 and 17591?",
    "answer": 52593
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4 and 5?",
    "answer": 9
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 788 and 669?",
    "answer": 1457
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7143 and 7488?",
    "answer": 14631
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9130 and 9538?",
    "answer": 18668
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6265 and 9560?",
    "answer": 15825
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 89 and 71?",
    "answer": 160
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2263014683 and 7622362020?",
    "answer": 9885376703
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 51729275 and 21795282?",
    "answer": 73524557
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5 and 6?",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1788954926 and 5896074647?",
    "answer": 7685029573
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 20 and 99?",
    "answer": 119
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 686757014 and 201605743?",
    "answer": 888362757
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 879589 and 724010?",
    "answer": 1603599
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 79 and 22?",
    "answer": 101
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 48246 and 33137?",
    "answer": 81383
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3006829 and 6137301?",
    "answer": 9144130
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6817 and 4895?",
    "answer": 11712
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1617 and 4033?",
    "answer": 5650
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2 and 2?",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3400 and 7584?",
    "answer": 10984
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 50819266 and 74142950?",
    "answer": 124962216
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 97268 and 80873?",
    "answer": 178141
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 87 and 88?",
    "answer": 175
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 10052 and 45108?",
    "answer": 55160
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1 and 1?",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 524 and 993?",
    "answer": 1517
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7081737 and 7934715?",
    "answer": 15016452
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8 and 8?",
    "answer": 16
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9911895 and 9777969?",
    "answer": 19689864
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 88866 and 56927?",
    "answer": 145793
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 237 and 717?",
    "answer": 954
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 76 and 79?",
    "answer": 155
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 48 and 12?",
    "answer": 60
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8313727834 and 4649054933?",
    "answer": 12962782767
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 487683734 and 981801544?",
    "answer": 1469485278
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2 and 4?",
    "answer": 6
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9323 and 9504?",
    "answer": 18827
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 651971 and 137744?",
    "answer": 789715
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 367635425 and 915387673?",
    "answer": 1283023098
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 51 and 58?",
    "answer": 109
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 891161556 and 364019418?",
    "answer": 1255180974
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 64990 and 17992?",
    "answer": 82982
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 17970034 and 49973441?",
    "answer": 67943475
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2925 and 5775?",
    "answer": 8700
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 72 and 77?",
    "answer": 149
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2622830 and 8066283?",
    "answer": 10689113
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4 and 5?",
    "answer": 9
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 925466 and 944242?",
    "answer": 1869708
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 76 and 61?",
    "answer": 137
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 26 and 30?",
    "answer": 56
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 544150 and 824709?",
    "answer": 1368859
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6672 and 8044?",
    "answer": 14716
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 74 and 92?",
    "answer": 166
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 523967862 and 593442471?",
    "answer": 1117410333
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 457953483 and 648188272?",
    "answer": 1106141755
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7815 and 7839?",
    "answer": 15654
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 52198518 and 86250406?",
    "answer": 138448924
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 565587 and 230710?",
    "answer": 796297
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2 and 1?",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 825709 and 823424?",
    "answer": 1649133
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 91830 and 96544?",
    "answer": 188374
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3886455817 and 4928009214?",
    "answer": 8814465031
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 627574919 and 411212216?",
    "answer": 1038787135
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2 and 8?",
    "answer": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2150648015 and 1174824705?",
    "answer": 3325472720
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1723895679 and 3806558380?",
    "answer": 5530454059
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 257389 and 208436?",
    "answer": 465825
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 229835947 and 192462137?",
    "answer": 422298084
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4360942 and 2770390?",
    "answer": 7131332
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 963 and 545?",
    "answer": 1508
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7 and 6?",
    "answer": 13
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4 and 1?",
    "answer": 5
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8241461 and 3975726?",
    "answer": 12217187
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 18 and 32?",
    "answer": 50
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 968 and 971?",
    "answer": 1939
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 179 and 673?",
    "answer": 852
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 479 and 343?",
    "answer": 822
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1663305318 and 9343791813?",
    "answer": 11007097131
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6542914721 and 6652502090?",
    "answer": 13195416811
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 50145 and 13408?",
    "answer": 63553
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7698 and 7051?",
    "answer": 14749
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 882 and 426?",
    "answer": 1308
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 757224 and 777735?",
    "answer": 1534959
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1469 and 1516?",
    "answer": 2985
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 582817689 and 898490115?",
    "answer": 1481307804
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 929884 and 545045?",
    "answer": 1474929
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4941972 and 9089947?",
    "answer": 14031919
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 46 and 43?",
    "answer": 89
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 72758434 and 15168982?",
    "answer": 87927416
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7521002303 and 6844729741?",
    "answer": 14365732044
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 86827 and 91978?",
    "answer": 178805
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 86 and 27?",
    "answer": 113
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 641 and 688?",
    "answer": 1329
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 40020 and 47554?",
    "answer": 87574
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 480 and 370?",
    "answer": 850
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 421 and 530?",
    "answer": 951
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 704360 and 632890?",
    "answer": 1337250
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 721556 and 144693?",
    "answer": 866249
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 882095 and 898801?",
    "answer": 1780896
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 315 and 364?",
    "answer": 679
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 941 and 104?",
    "answer": 1045
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3 and 1?",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 555328 and 141618?",
    "answer": 696946
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 88 and 40?",
    "answer": 128
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 929243 and 431475?",
    "answer": 1360718
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 28 and 61?",
    "answer": 89
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 36944 and 61253?",
    "answer": 98197
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 37 and 33?",
    "answer": 70
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 24 and 32?",
    "answer": 56
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6028 and 7124?",
    "answer": 13152
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6448857 and 3432641?",
    "answer": 9881498
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 48877268 and 95178465?",
    "answer": 144055733
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 24 and 10?",
    "answer": 34
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 108258 and 821531?",
    "answer": 929789
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5481822514 and 3813823258?",
    "answer": 9295645772
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1 and 2?",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3229896451 and 5376935392?",
    "answer": 8606831843
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 49 and 59?",
    "answer": 108
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 900326846 and 561165335?",
    "answer": 1461492181
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 36061 and 61134?",
    "answer": 97195
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 29062966 and 55987583?",
    "answer": 85050549
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9 and 8?",
    "answer": 17
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6214510 and 9371134?",
    "answer": 15585644
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9603933279 and 3032062521?",
    "answer": 12635995800
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 73683913 and 34914700?",
    "answer": 108598613
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 86695 and 61612?",
    "answer": 148307
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6458762035 and 1395322081?",
    "answer": 7854084116
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 386422 and 679823?",
    "answer": 1066245
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4721758 and 3860381?",
    "answer": 8582139
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7 and 8?",
    "answer": 15
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 91944 and 37971?",
    "answer": 129915
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 44 and 42?",
    "answer": 86
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 226880775 and 214361115?",
    "answer": 441241890
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 87450 and 93221?",
    "answer": 180671
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5232 and 2169?",
    "answer": 7401
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 886747 and 571516?",
    "answer": 1458263
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5019 and 5621?",
    "answer": 10640
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 611571 and 117740?",
    "answer": 729311
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 393068293 and 701249338?",
    "answer": 1094317631
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 20 and 28?",
    "answer": 48
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3879082848 and 2012350996?",
    "answer": 5891433844
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 145122 and 395242?",
    "answer": 540364
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2653432439 and 1015497453?",
    "answer": 3668929892
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 93 and 87?",
    "answer": 180
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 583503384 and 165510419?",
    "answer": 749013803
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 82322 and 37499?",
    "answer": 119821
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8815840458 and 8155370643?",
    "answer": 16971211101
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1601830009 and 6649370439?",
    "answer": 8251200448
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 50752 and 76140?",
    "answer": 126892
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 22598949 and 29408091?",
    "answer": 52007040
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4715188717 and 6465240261?",
    "answer": 11180428978
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3396599 and 5808241?",
    "answer": 9204840
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 28 and 22?",
    "answer": 50
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 292523 and 553690?",
    "answer": 846213
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9163097009 and 5312431229?",
    "answer": 14475528238
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7673 and 5341?",
    "answer": 13014
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 63232 and 38696?",
    "answer": 101928
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 363646 and 224850?",
    "answer": 588496
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 304 and 980?",
    "answer": 1284
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 133494 and 520515?",
    "answer": 654009
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5 and 1?",
    "answer": 6
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 49887 and 61070?",
    "answer": 110957
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 38475 and 68288?",
    "answer": 106763
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 83885 and 63443?",
    "answer": 147328
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 816463 and 225580?",
    "answer": 1042043
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 73 and 80?",
    "answer": 153
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2689 and 1935?",
    "answer": 4624
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 291147 and 786529?",
    "answer": 1077676
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 429 and 325?",
    "answer": 754
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2 and 2?",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6010 and 3495?",
    "answer": 9505
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 202491848 and 637002340?",
    "answer": 839494188
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 259269770 and 696261960?",
    "answer": 955531730
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9 and 8?",
    "answer": 17
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7517278743 and 4123746782?",
    "answer": 11641025525
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 41083 and 91769?",
    "answer": 132852
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9821844168 and 6841141048?",
    "answer": 16662985216
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2464 and 7206?",
    "answer": 9670
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8857485920 and 1609992213?",
    "answer": 10467478133
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 11129 and 83800?",
    "answer": 94929
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 872008 and 163258?",
    "answer": 1035266
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 943 and 234?",
    "answer": 1177
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 36613222 and 27691981?",
    "answer": 64305203
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 383056714 and 710140718?",
    "answer": 1093197432
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 22 and 28?",
    "answer": 50
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 19287 and 75357?",
    "answer": 94644
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8791183 and 6918439?",
    "answer": 15709622
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 28765 and 67451?",
    "answer": 96216
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5254 and 2680?",
    "answer": 7934
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 977784 and 966569?",
    "answer": 1944353
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 66264845 and 20039929?",
    "answer": 86304774
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8940147 and 1187006?",
    "answer": 10127153
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3 and 6?",
    "answer": 9
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 58 and 40?",
    "answer": 98
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 322 and 820?",
    "answer": 1142
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3 and 1?",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 99833947 and 24131360?",
    "answer": 123965307
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 868 and 732?",
    "answer": 1600
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 751960671 and 174338130?",
    "answer": 926298801
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 909767 and 239320?",
    "answer": 1149087
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 74 and 91?",
    "answer": 165
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 58167 and 38782?",
    "answer": 96949
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1975847 and 7802896?",
    "answer": 9778743
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 49362154 and 74490086?",
    "answer": 123852240
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1957327565 and 4013470451?",
    "answer": 5970798016
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 642277986 and 500363304?",
    "answer": 1142641290
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6404503 and 5369848?",
    "answer": 11774351
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1 and 4?",
    "answer": 5
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 772982 and 277789?",
    "answer": 1050771
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 17424 and 15429?",
    "answer": 32853
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 39 and 59?",
    "answer": 98
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 57 and 39?",
    "answer": 96
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 631731 and 479998?",
    "answer": 1111729
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 306 and 785?",
    "answer": 1091
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 37289108 and 40932464?",
    "answer": 78221572
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 797653844 and 350267592?",
    "answer": 1147921436
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2799856180 and 2869274635?",
    "answer": 5669130815
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3952030 and 8515926?",
    "answer": 12467956
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 650099617 and 650944743?",
    "answer": 1301044360
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 480693370 and 182482822?",
    "answer": 663176192
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 85368 and 39214?",
    "answer": 124582
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2 and 2?",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 566297 and 288187?",
    "answer": 854484
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 527162380 and 808811892?",
    "answer": 1335974272
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 689527435 and 107446997?",
    "answer": 796974432
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 46620 and 35106?",
    "answer": 81726
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3873516417 and 9900526328?",
    "answer": 13774042745
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 18442 and 89687?",
    "answer": 108129
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9217544 and 1376542?",
    "answer": 10594086
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 873617572 and 392103799?",
    "answer": 1265721371
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8978223196 and 3645320641?",
    "answer": 12623543837
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5 and 9?",
    "answer": 14
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 58273157 and 71566946?",
    "answer": 129840103
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 663519446 and 337497964?",
    "answer": 1001017410
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 414445462 and 296833166?",
    "answer": 711278628
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 977113 and 322318?",
    "answer": 1299431
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 87601 and 55384?",
    "answer": 142985
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 168 and 548?",
    "answer": 716
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9501015354 and 8030768863?",
    "answer": 17531784217
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 251 and 628?",
    "answer": 879
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 849 and 920?",
    "answer": 1769
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2648228507 and 2382490762?",
    "answer": 5030719269
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8617633126 and 4361626552?",
    "answer": 12979259678
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9227222927 and 5389463616?",
    "answer": 14616686543
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 79276 and 18322?",
    "answer": 97598
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6855 and 5234?",
    "answer": 12089
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8257 and 1090?",
    "answer": 9347
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1801435719 and 7769362633?",
    "answer": 9570798352
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6 and 9?",
    "answer": 15
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4 and 6?",
    "answer": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1339516 and 6325017?",
    "answer": 7664533
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 54821879 and 13725970?",
    "answer": 68547849
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1604238238 and 3008867608?",
    "answer": 4613105846
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 347 and 979?",
    "answer": 1326
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4 and 9?",
    "answer": 13
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 40341 and 21495?",
    "answer": 61836
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 472 and 945?",
    "answer": 1417
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 875831496 and 783991654?",
    "answer": 1659823150
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 731502 and 269869?",
    "answer": 1001371
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5 and 9?",
    "answer": 14
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 91770155 and 28913039?",
    "answer": 120683194
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 137 and 813?",
    "answer": 950
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 41 and 88?",
    "answer": 129
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6631205648 and 1392148567?",
    "answer": 8023354215
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 703 and 125?",
    "answer": 828
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 12817 and 62003?",
    "answer": 74820
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2041049 and 9331763?",
    "answer": 11372812
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 93995537 and 44523624?",
    "answer": 138519161
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 23452546 and 15676045?",
    "answer": 39128591
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6 and 3?",
    "answer": 9
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 30 and 40?",
    "answer": 70
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 48868276 and 70373379?",
    "answer": 119241655
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8833411955 and 6027777498?",
    "answer": 14861189453
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 45863126 and 66511347?",
    "answer": 112374473
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 47 and 11?",
    "answer": 58
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 987858579 and 260090924?",
    "answer": 1247949503
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 515664578 and 219393904?",
    "answer": 735058482
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7222384407 and 4400912392?",
    "answer": 11623296799
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 379925 and 598476?",
    "answer": 978401
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 466 and 892?",
    "answer": 1358
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 75915272 and 71244309?",
    "answer": 147159581
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5447090084 and 6922905056?",
    "answer": 12369995140
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 891 and 500?",
    "answer": 1391
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 26382695 and 45547052?",
    "answer": 71929747
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 32559 and 27640?",
    "answer": 60199
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 39089 and 21748?",
    "answer": 60837
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8 and 6?",
    "answer": 14
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 141 and 983?",
    "answer": 1124
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 11032 and 46503?",
    "answer": 57535
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9450101103 and 2137563060?",
    "answer": 11587664163
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 90789193 and 87176676?",
    "answer": 177965869
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3138 and 2505?",
    "answer": 5643
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1368226431 and 6627207622?",
    "answer": 7995434053
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7 and 9?",
    "answer": 16
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7222 and 7594?",
    "answer": 14816
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6043 and 6805?",
    "answer": 12848
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3922712 and 7657951?",
    "answer": 11580663
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 98 and 65?",
    "answer": 163
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6903296 and 6804472?",
    "answer": 13707768
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 39790161 and 71580654?",
    "answer": 111370815
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 87 and 68?",
    "answer": 155
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4882608 and 2700597?",
    "answer": 7583205
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 923916210 and 999031499?",
    "answer": 1922947709
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9279426 and 7066610?",
    "answer": 16346036
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 26 and 18?",
    "answer": 44
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7531 and 2354?",
    "answer": 9885
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 467 and 475?",
    "answer": 942
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 462683774 and 288756066?",
    "answer": 751439840
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 598 and 736?",
    "answer": 1334
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4989 and 2122?",
    "answer": 7111
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 96787735 and 70701239?",
    "answer": 167488974
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 75 and 31?",
    "answer": 106
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 186 and 140?",
    "answer": 326
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 31050 and 92004?",
    "answer": 123054
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1 and 8?",
    "answer": 9
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8906 and 7047?",
    "answer": 15953
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 74999147 and 78342197?",
    "answer": 153341344
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 35525471 and 40128875?",
    "answer": 75654346
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 273 and 381?",
    "answer": 654
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2 and 4?",
    "answer": 6
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 491 and 595?",
    "answer": 1086
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 93333428 and 94115097?",
    "answer": 187448525
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 707 and 215?",
    "answer": 922
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 87 and 10?",
    "answer": 97
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2577311 and 1416374?",
    "answer": 3993685
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8562783302 and 1276618721?",
    "answer": 9839402023
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 52 and 43?",
    "answer": 95
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3793339366 and 2950868139?",
    "answer": 6744207505
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8943298 and 9239395?",
    "answer": 18182693
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6 and 6?",
    "answer": 12
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 463190 and 931586?",
    "answer": 1394776
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3 and 4?",
    "answer": 7
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 28399091 and 64497985?",
    "answer": 92897076
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6910895 and 4093384?",
    "answer": 11004279
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4432 and 5128?",
    "answer": 9560
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 41950813 and 58599717?",
    "answer": 100550530
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 457893475 and 785525369?",
    "answer": 1243418844
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6754180383 and 4848720827?",
    "answer": 11602901210
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5 and 4?",
    "answer": 9
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 66990 and 55588?",
    "answer": 122578
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4 and 3?",
    "answer": 7
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1695161 and 8803712?",
    "answer": 10498873
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7528069182 and 4539544723?",
    "answer": 12067613905
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 36236968 and 65906343?",
    "answer": 102143311
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3193813 and 4337075?",
    "answer": 7530888
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 175819 and 439808?",
    "answer": 615627
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5152522 and 7394597?",
    "answer": 12547119
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6723612 and 2489496?",
    "answer": 9213108
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 40 and 68?",
    "answer": 108
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1299603 and 3449808?",
    "answer": 4749411
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9036707 and 6329170?",
    "answer": 15365877
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 98931 and 25226?",
    "answer": 124157
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 575927609 and 817766251?",
    "answer": 1393693860
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6692436669 and 2925581559?",
    "answer": 9618018228
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 11 and 81?",
    "answer": 92
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 843652475 and 196357205?",
    "answer": 1040009680
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 61891 and 50061?",
    "answer": 111952
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3 and 5?",
    "answer": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 52352473 and 12426311?",
    "answer": 64778784
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 316 and 678?",
    "answer": 994
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8325199 and 3667959?",
    "answer": 11993158
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 331 and 969?",
    "answer": 1300
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 511546684 and 610835640?",
    "answer": 1122382324
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 37 and 73?",
    "answer": 110
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 586463 and 435225?",
    "answer": 1021688
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 90940644 and 64330644?",
    "answer": 155271288
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2026913126 and 7493320790?",
    "answer": 9520233916
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 27199 and 62115?",
    "answer": 89314
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2720 and 2486?",
    "answer": 5206
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 45576 and 48509?",
    "answer": 94085
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4654705779 and 3401036880?",
    "answer": 8055742659
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 99787 and 72982?",
    "answer": 172769
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 117304570 and 290563618?",
    "answer": 407868188
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4724 and 2430?",
    "answer": 7154
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9650164 and 7861997?",
    "answer": 17512161
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 645344484 and 942635898?",
    "answer": 1587980382
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 14 and 69?",
    "answer": 83
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 201369 and 504255?",
    "answer": 705624
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 558164 and 638888?",
    "answer": 1197052
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5 and 7?",
    "answer": 12
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 501077 and 705395?",
    "answer": 1206472
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 71575915 and 17224687?",
    "answer": 88800602
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 12537 and 74160?",
    "answer": 86697
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 986 and 638?",
    "answer": 1624
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 191841628 and 938307415?",
    "answer": 1130149043
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 80 and 96?",
    "answer": 176
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 696406 and 223530?",
    "answer": 919936
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 97 and 24?",
    "answer": 121
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6 and 1?",
    "answer": 7
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6452332 and 3794489?",
    "answer": 10246821
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 802990 and 467109?",
    "answer": 1270099
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7881030 and 2477966?",
    "answer": 10358996
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3206 and 3359?",
    "answer": 6565
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 350442587 and 709765123?",
    "answer": 1060207710
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9758 and 6851?",
    "answer": 16609
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 931432 and 552543?",
    "answer": 1483975
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2897 and 6866?",
    "answer": 9763
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4654137 and 5221731?",
    "answer": 9875868
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6661228254 and 3056300268?",
    "answer": 9717528522
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 92797 and 25738?",
    "answer": 118535
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3571 and 9734?",
    "answer": 13305
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 47615 and 72502?",
    "answer": 120117
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6149394 and 1696413?",
    "answer": 7845807
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6549 and 8812?",
    "answer": 15361
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6853941 and 9824846?",
    "answer": 16678787
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 146545 and 751909?",
    "answer": 898454
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 863145299 and 845793539?",
    "answer": 1708938838
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 27098 and 63049?",
    "answer": 90147
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 581041678 and 585903586?",
    "answer": 1166945264
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 621772 and 194029?",
    "answer": 815801
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8016105232 and 2050284906?",
    "answer": 10066390138
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9977520978 and 4643562770?",
    "answer": 14621083748
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 236 and 483?",
    "answer": 719
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6 and 5?",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 144083130 and 207203971?",
    "answer": 351287101
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4399 and 4736?",
    "answer": 9135
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 39931650 and 49116041?",
    "answer": 89047691
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 32881 and 16923?",
    "answer": 49804
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1412143632 and 8563274311?",
    "answer": 9975417943
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7149247 and 7974656?",
    "answer": 15123903
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 62 and 25?",
    "answer": 87
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 81410448 and 77153920?",
    "answer": 158564368
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 52622398 and 84839182?",
    "answer": 137461580
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 28929 and 46355?",
    "answer": 75284
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6635 and 2343?",
    "answer": 8978
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 123 and 932?",
    "answer": 1055
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 890931 and 458113?",
    "answer": 1349044
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 296 and 475?",
    "answer": 771
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 91362 and 30092?",
    "answer": 121454
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 728 and 534?",
    "answer": 1262
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 21895218 and 52841959?",
    "answer": 74737177
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9085215160 and 5948240354?",
    "answer": 15033455514
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4 and 7?",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 68 and 25?",
    "answer": 93
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7948 and 6717?",
    "answer": 14665
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6560 and 2332?",
    "answer": 8892
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 796 and 312?",
    "answer": 1108
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 19782 and 25097?",
    "answer": 44879
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 125082474 and 491536581?",
    "answer": 616619055
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3879047937 and 9893738424?",
    "answer": 13772786361
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 928339495 and 641940387?",
    "answer": 1570279882
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 61 and 59?",
    "answer": 120
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 74693591 and 96079685?",
    "answer": 170773276
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9336753394 and 8875319798?",
    "answer": 18212073192
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2 and 4?",
    "answer": 6
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 11807898 and 31632117?",
    "answer": 43440015
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4758771253 and 8712901373?",
    "answer": 13471672626
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 315 and 339?",
    "answer": 654
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4478152 and 7222249?",
    "answer": 11700401
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 98027 and 91932?",
    "answer": 189959
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3 and 3?",
    "answer": 6
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 714148 and 805481?",
    "answer": 1519629
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8 and 5?",
    "answer": 13
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 404 and 442?",
    "answer": 846
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 87 and 36?",
    "answer": 123
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 56880 and 26114?",
    "answer": 82994
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2144 and 5560?",
    "answer": 7704
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7 and 1?",
    "answer": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 12003716 and 64387561?",
    "answer": 76391277
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2093726 and 6233556?",
    "answer": 8327282
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9 and 2?",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 47335500 and 53505765?",
    "answer": 100841265
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 28438 and 99992?",
    "answer": 128430
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 3029832257 and 7318303496?",
    "answer": 10348135753
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 39 and 16?",
    "answer": 55
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 383 and 848?",
    "answer": 1231
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 25758 and 26783?",
    "answer": 52541
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1 and 2?",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 30943 and 19775?",
    "answer": 50718
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 829388086 and 250208939?",
    "answer": 1079597025
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 51344444 and 72834379?",
    "answer": 124178823
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1 and 8?",
    "answer": 9
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 2879547 and 5151124?",
    "answer": 8030671
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 671817059 and 881385631?",
    "answer": 1553202690
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 7444627 and 4131564?",
    "answer": 11576191
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 27 and 76?",
    "answer": 103
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 10 and 20?",
    "answer": 30
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8423775 and 4039893?",
    "answer": 12463668
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 46272698 and 75469074?",
    "answer": 121741772
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5560 and 7609?",
    "answer": 13169
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 480722960 and 962560717?",
    "answer": 1443283677
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 766662 and 474806?",
    "answer": 1241468
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 68883269 and 82563938?",
    "answer": 151447207
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 4 and 7?",
    "answer": 11
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 283 and 100?",
    "answer": 383
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 94119531 and 53930989?",
    "answer": 148050520
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 608137216 and 334940644?",
    "answer": 943077860
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 360 and 416?",
    "answer": 776
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 64184239 and 84348199?",
    "answer": 148532438
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 5327 and 2646?",
    "answer": 7973
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 238 and 939?",
    "answer": 1177
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 68660066 and 90380981?",
    "answer": 159041047
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 9016 and 7030?",
    "answer": 16046
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 915571014 and 771256382?",
    "answer": 1686827396
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 6062852028 and 1837573040?",
    "answer": 7900425068
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 8095702252 and 5832930414?",
    "answer": 13928632666
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 807820 and 953746?",
    "answer": 1761566
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1359134 and 3499761?",
    "answer": 4858895
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 1 and 3?",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 78234223 and 77203819?",
    "answer": 155438042
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 97575 and 66137?",
    "answer": 163712
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 688 and 157?",
    "answer": 845
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 65939 and 69097?",
    "answer": 135036
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the sum of 237109030 and 609621866?",
    "answer": 846730896
  }
]